<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<source>
   <publisher>Ohio Means Jobs</publisher>
   <publisherurl>https://drive.google.com/uc?id=1hBNIXQbyZIEp4HHAI0HvDwYRkGucLQUl&amp;export=download&amp;confirm=t</publisherurl>
   <lastBuildDate>2022-12-06</lastBuildDate>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Office I / Customer Service (Fairfield)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237182611]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-10]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237182611]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[WILSONART LLC]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Fairfield]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45014]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<STRONG>Wilsonart</STRONG><br><br>Wilsonart Flagg Inc., is seeking to f ill an opening for an Office I/Customer Service. <br> This individual is part of our small Customer Service team in Fairfield , Ohio. This person will work directly with our customers and will be required to enter electronic orders, answer phone calls, respond to customer inquiries, as well as a variety of other tasks as required. This position performs extensive data entry into our internal system. <br> <br> ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES <br> <UL><LI> Performs duties in accordance with specific instructions and established work methods </LI><LI> Enters orders via 10 key into internal system </LI><LI> Resolves routine questions and problems via phone, email, and occasionally in person <br> Assists the needs of the customer </LI><LI> Knowledge of basic accounting skills applying payments, issuing credits <br> Helping maintain customer aging levels <br> Good understanding of Excel as well as Outlook </LI><LI> Maintain good communication/relationships with customers concerning account status </LI></UL> <br><br>KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS, AND ABILITIES <br><br><UL><LI> Skill in resolving routine questions and problems </LI><LI> Experience with Microsoft Office Suite, especially Outlook </LI><LI> Skill in data entry (10 key) </LI><LI> Ability to follow directions, take notes, and self-start </LI><LI> Ability to work under direct supervision </LI><LI> Ability to multi-task, while staying organized </LI></UL><br><br>MINIMUM REQUIREMENTS <br> <br> EDUCATION: <br><br> High School Graduate or GED <br> <br> EXPERIENCE: <br><br> 1+ years <br><br> Fifteen semester hours of college in a related field may substitute for the required experience <br> <br> PHYSICAL REQUIREMENTS: Sitting in the same location of standing/walking; required to stoop, climb or lift light material (10-20lbs) or equipment. <br> <br> ENVIRONMENT: Located in a comfortable indoor area. Examples: executive, management and support positions <br><br> Wilsonart is an Equal Opportunity / Affirmative Action employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration without regard to sex, gender identity, sexual orientation, race, color, religion, national origin, disability, protected veteran status, age, or any other characteristic protected by law. <br><br>Wilsonart is an Equal Opportunity / Affirmative Action employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability, or protected veteran status.<br><br>Apply Here <br><br>PI164627625]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Other]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Luisa Hernandez</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[jt.sjb@jobtarget.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Mobile Security Officer (Cleveland)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237275029]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237275029]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Cleveland]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44114]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheSecurity Officerposition helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjg2MDU5LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Greeter (Birchaven, PRN) (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237275186]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237275186]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION <br><br>The primary purpose of this position is to welcome visitors and direct them in an efficient manner, in accordance with established procedures, and as directed by your manager.<br><br>JOB DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES<br><br>Duty 1: Adhere to Birchaven policies and procedures and abide by Birchaven ethical statement and resident's rights.<br><br>Duty 2: Receive and follow Greeter schedule/instructions from supervisor as outlined in our established policies and procedures.<br><br>Duty 3: Transport visitors and guests, when needed, on the golf cart.<br><br>Duty 4: Answer telephone, determine nature of call, and relay information within the facility as necessary.<br><br>Duty 5: Receive inquiries and release information in accordance with established policies and procedures.<br><br>Duty 6: Give directions/information to appropriate manages immediately.<br><br>Duty 7: Receive guests/visitors ensuring they abide by existing rules.<br><br>Duty 8: Sort the mail.<br><br>Duty 9: General typing/correspondence as required.<br><br>Duty10: Create and maintain an atmosphere of warmth, personal interest, and positive emphasis, as well as, a calm environment throughout the facility.<br><br>Duty 11: Maintain confidentiality of all pertinent patient care information to assure patient rights are protected.<br><br>Duty 12 Attend all monthly meetings.<br><br>Duty 13 Attend all mandatory training sessions.<br><br>Duty 14: Other related duties as may become necessary or as directed by Manager.<br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Exceptional customer service. <br>* General clerical skills <br>* Knowledge of Microsoft, Word, Excel & Outlook. <br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS<br><br>This position requires a full range of body motions with intermittent walking, lifting, bending, squatting, kneeling, twisting, and standing. The associate will be required to walk for up to one hour a day, sit for four to six hours a day and stand for one hour a day. The individual must have good eye-hand coordination and fine finger dexterity for simple grasping tasks. The individual must have excellent verbal communication skills to perform daily tasks. The associate must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. The individual must be able to operate the golf cart safely.Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjUyMjg3LjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Mobile Security Officer (Akron)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237275324]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237275324]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Akron]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44308]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Mobile Officer<br><br>We help make your world a safer place.<br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients.<br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. The Mobile Officer position helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, which may include operating a vehicle to patrol. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values of Integrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness. These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions.<br><br>The Mobile Officer maintains the security and safety of multiple sites by conducting patrols via a motor vehicle. All you need is a valid driver's license and clean driving history, to be a great fit for this role! No experience? No problem! With a friendly and positive attitude we will provide the training and knowledge you need to be successful in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team?<br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home<br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide.<br><br>See a different world.<br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjc1MTI3LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Chrysler Security Officer (Toledo)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237276136]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237276136]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Toledo]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[43607]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. The Security Officer position helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our client by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values of Integrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness. These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>Our Security Officer positions are highly sought after. If you have retail, customer service or hospitality industry experience you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjAxMjE2LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Machine Builder - B Shift (Sandusky)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237276251]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237276251]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[John Bean Technologies Corporation]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Sandusky]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44870]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<STRONG>JBT Corporation</STRONG><br><br>AN EQUAL OPPORTUNITY EMPLOYER<br><br>It is the policy of JBT Corporation to provide equal opportunity for qualified persons and not to discriminate against any applicant for employment because of race, color, religion, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, disability, veteran status, citizenship, or any other characteristic protected by federal, state or local law at the JBT Corporation location to which this application is submitted. In addition, as a Federal Government contractor, JBT Corporation is an affirmative action employer. If you require accommodation during the application process, please contact the local Human Resources department. EOE-Females/Minorities/Protected Veterans/Individuals with Disabilities<br><br>If you have a disability or impairment that prevents you from completing the online application, please seek the assistance of your local employment services agency. JBT maintains active relationships with local employment services agencies, and they have pledged their support in assisting any applicant needing help in applying. To find information on agencies throughout the United States, please go to www.careeronestop.org<br><br>You may also call Megan Meagrow at 844-286-4524 if your disability or impairment prevents you from applying online. NOTE: Do not use this number unless you need assistance because of a disability or impairment. The personnel attending this phone line will not be able to give you a status update regarding your application and will not be the individuals making a decision regarding your employment.<br><br><STRONG>Machine Builder - B Shift</STRONG><br><br>US-OH-Sandusky<br><br><STRONG>Job ID:</STRONG> 2022-8579<br><STRONG>Type:</STRONG> Regular Full-Time<br><STRONG># of Openings:</STRONG> 4<br><STRONG>Category:</STRONG> Direct Labor<br><br>JBT Corporation<br><br><STRONG>Overview</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>Overview </STRONG><br><br>JBT is a diverse, global company with many needs for international management talent and great opportunities for experienced graduates Our businesses are worldwide and opportunities are broad in scope<br><br><STRONG>Start your career with us</STRONG><br><br>Being a global company allows us to present you with a number of career opportunities JBT is one of the largest solutions providers to the global food processing industry The largest food processors within the fruit, vegetable, meat, poultry, seafood and bakery industries are among our customers<br><br><STRONG>PAY - $19 - $27/hr based on experience/education</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>BENEFITS - </STRONG><STRONG> Start from day 1! </STRONG><br><br>JBT Corporation offers the growth potential of a company with a developing technology that is unique in its field, plus frequent company-sponsored events and a competitive benefits package that includes:<br><UL><LI>Medical, Dental, Vision coverage</LI><LI>401(k) plan with company match - up to 65%</LI><LI>Company paid Short Term Disability, Long Term Disability, and Life Insurance</LI><LI>Paid Parental Leave</LI><LI>Paid Holidays</LI><LI>Vacation pay</LI><LI>Sick pay</LI><LI>Annual Bonus Pay</LI><LI>Tuition Reimbursement (*eligible after 2 years)</LI></UL><br><br><STRONG>Responsibilities</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>B Shift with $070/hr shift differential - $500 Sign-On Bonus!</STRONG><br><br>Successful applicants must be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment Vaccine verification will be required upon acceptance of employment <br> <LI>Fits and assembles components according to assembly blueprints, manuals, engineering memos, sketches, and knowledge of machine construction to construct, rebuild, and repair machines and equipment, using handtools and power tools</LI><LI>Analyzes assembly blueprint and specifications manual, and plans machine building operations</LI><LI>Verifies conformance of parts to stock list and blueprints, using measuring instruments, such as calipers, gauges, and micrometers</LI><LI>Responsible for quality control Make adjustments as necessary to produce product within specifications Reject product outside of specifications</LI><LI>Operate within standard operating procedures (SOPs) and Job Safety Analysis (JSAs)</LI><LI>Complete daily production logs</LI> <br><br><STRONG>Qualifications</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>KNOWLEDGE AND SKILL REQUIREMENTS</STRONG><br> <LI>Basic reading, writing, and arithmetic skills required This is normally acquired through a high school diploma or equivalent experience</LI><LI>Previous Manufacturing Experience preferred</LI><LI>Previous Mechanical Working Experience preferred</LI><LI>Manual dexterity required for operating machinery and computers</LI><LI>Ability to lift up to 30 pounds required</LI> <br><STRONG>WORKING CONDITIONS</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>NOISE LEVEL:</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>Exposure Level</STRONG><br> <br>Very quiet<br>  <br>Quiet<br>  <br>Moderate<br>  <br>Loud<br> <br>X<br> <br>Very Loud<br><br><STRONG>VISION DEMANDS:</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>Required</STRONG><br> <br>No special vision requirements<br>  <br>Close vision (distance of 20 inches or less)<br> <br>X<br> <br>Distance vision (distance of 20 feet or more)<br> <br>X<br> <br>Color vision (able to identify/distinguish colors)<br> <br>X<br> <br>Peripheral vision<br><br>Depth perception<br> <br>X<br> <br>Ability to adjust focus<br> <br>X<br><br><STRONG>PHYSICAL ACTIVITIES:</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>Amount of Time</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>N/A</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>Under 1/3</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>1/3 to 2/3</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>Over 2/3</STRONG><br> <br>Stand<br>   <br>X<br>  <br>Walk<br>  <br>X<br>   <br>Sit<br>  <br>X<br>  <br>X<br> <br>Dexterity - Use hands to finger, handle or feed<br>   <br>X<br>  <br>Reach with hands and arms<br>   <br>X<br>  <br>Climb or balance<br>  <br>X<br>   <br>Stoop, kneel, crouch, or crawl<br>   <br>X<br>  <br>Talk<br>   <br>X<br>  <br>Hear<br>   <br>X<br>  <br><STRONG>WEIGHT and FORCE DEMANDS:</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>Amount of Time</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>N/A</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>Under 1/3</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>1/3 to 2/3</STRONG><br> <br><STRONG>Over 2/3</STRONG><br> <br>Up to 25 pounds<br>   <br>X<br>  <br>Up to 50 pounds<br>   <br>X<br><br>You may also call 844-286-4524 if your disability or impairment prevents you from applying online NOTE: Do not use this number unless you need assistance because of a disability or i<br><br>Apply Here <br><br>PI164759328]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Other]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Luisa Hernandez</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[jt.sjb@jobtarget.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[PRODUCTION SUPERVISOR (Fremont)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236084535]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-13]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236084535]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Ardagh Metal Beverage USA Inc.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Fremont]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[43420]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Summary: Supervises and coordinates activities of production crew members engaged in operating variety of machines to manufacture cans. <br><br>Essential Duties and Responsibilities include the following. Other duties may be assigned. <br><br>* Review production schedule and coordinate runs according to schedule. <br>* Review crew manning and assign employees to ensure that positions are covered. <br>* Interfaces with others in the organization to ensure customer deadlines are met. <br>* Inspects and measures parts and products to verify conformance to specifications. <br>* Communicate with crew members regarding adjusting machines and equipment which fail to meet standards. <br>* Recommends and implements measures to improve production methods, equipment performance, and quality of product. <br>* Analyzes and resolves work problems, or assists workers in solving work problems. <br>* Maintains accurate and timely labor, labor hours, spoilage and production production records. <br><br>Ardagh Group is a global leader in metal and glass packaging solutions, producing packaging for the world's leading brands. We trace our roots all the way back to the Irish Glass Bottle Company, founded in 1932. Since then, we have grown rapidly to a team of more than 16,000 people with yearly revenues of approximately $7 billion. Today, we have a presence across Europe and the Americas.<br><br>Did you know....<br><br>* Ardagh produces many of the beverage cans and bottles you drink your favorite beverages from? <br>* Metal and glass packaging we produce are permanent materials, meaning they can be infinitely recycled without any loss of quality? <br>* We produce more than 160 million containers per day across the country? <br>* Ardagh Metal Beverage North America produces more than 15 billion cans and can ends annually? <br>* Approximately 75% of aluminum ever produced is still in use today? <br>* Aluminum cans, with 73%, have the highest recycled content among all beverage containers? <br>Ardagh is passionate about sustainability and has a reputation for innovation. We push the boundaries of what's possible, pioneering new production methods, new design techniques and new ways to recycle and save energy. Our aim is to reduce any negative environmental impact while remaining economically sustainable and socially responsible.<br><br>Ardagh Group North America has been and will continue to be an equal opportunity employer. All employment decisions are made without regard to sex, gender (including pregnancy, childbirth, breast feeding, and related conditions), sexual orientation, gender identity, gender expression, race, creed, religion (including religious dress and grooming), color, national origin, ancestry (including association, affiliation, or participation with persons or activities related to national origin, English-proficiency or accent, or immigration status), physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, marital or domestic partner status, age, veteran or military status or any other basis prohibited by federal, state, or local law. Discrimination against any employee or applicant based on any of these factors is prohibited.<br><br>For more information on Ardagh Group, visit www.ardaghgroup.com.<br><br>Nearest Major Market: Toledo <br>Nearest Secondary Market: ClevelandApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjI3MDU2LjEwNTA4QGFyZGFnaGNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Manufacturing/Production/Operations]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Heather Bowling</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[heather.bowling@ardaghgroup.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Entry Level Machine Operator (Johnstown)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236110765]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-14]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236110765]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Mohawk ESV, Inc.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Johnstown]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[43031]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Requisition ID: 50981 <br><br>Entry Level Machine Operator <br><br>Are you looking for more? <br><br>At Mohawk Industries, we're committed to more - more customer solutions, more process improvements, more sustainable manufacturing and more opportunities for our team. <br><br>As a Fortune 500, global flooring leader with some of the best-known brands in the industry, Mohawk is a great place to start or develop your career with an emphasis on more of what's important to you. Whether you want to lead more, innovate more, learn more or create more, you can find your more with Mohawk. <br><br>Responsibilities: <br>*$1,000 Sign-On Bonus Available* <br><br>* Responsible for inspection and general upkeep of the lift truck assigned. <br>* Inspects lift truck and completes the inspection report for daily maintenance and safety purposes. <br>* Changes battery and cleans lift truck as needed. <br>* Pulls correct scrap foam material according to the particular product being produced. <br>* Places the proper material on the conveyor as determined by the production schedule and process flow. <br>* Maintains adequate amount of materials at the workstation at all times to ensure an even flow through the granulating process. <br>* Operates granulator equipment and monitors the process to ensure no contaminated material enters the equipment. <br>* Performs general housekeeping duties to maintain a clean and safe working environment. <br>* Serves as a member of the Plant Emergency Response Team <br>* Performs other duties as required. <br><br>Qualifications: <br><br>* Must be at least 18 years old. <br>* Prior experience operating a lift truck preferred. <br>* One year of related experience in a production environment. <br>* Ability to maintain an acceptable level of attendance in accordance with company and department guidelines. <br>* Must be able to Read & Write English <br>* Basic computer knowledge required <br>* Able to work in extreme temperatures. <br>* Able to sit, stand, reach, bend, climb and twist without restrictions. <br>* Able to stand for extended periods of time. <br>* Good oral and written communication skills to effectively interact with employees in the immediate unit and in related support roles. <br>* Ability to read and interpret documents such as safety rules, operating or maintenance instructions, and procedure manuals. <br>* Ability to add, subtract, multiply, and divide in all units of measure using whole numbers, decimals, and fractions. <br>* Requires a high degree of mental and visual attention to perform all tasks in a safe manner . <br><br>Mohawk Industries is a leading global flooring manufacturer that creates products to enhance residential and commercial spaces around the world. Mohawk's vertically integrated manufacturing and distribution processes provide competitive advantages in the production of carpet, rugs, ceramic tile, laminate, wood, stone and vinyl flooring. Our industry-leading innovation has yielded products and technologies that differentiate our brands in the marketplace and satisfy all remodeling and new construction requirements. Our brands are among the most recognized in the industry and include American Olean, Daltile, Durkan, IVC, Karastan, Marazzi, Mohawk, Mohawk Home, Pergo, and Quick-Step. During the past decade, Mohawk has transformed its business from an American carpet manufacturer into the world's largest flooring company with operations in Australia, Brazil, Canada, Europe, India, Malaysia, Mexico, New Zealand, Russia and the United States. <br><br>Mohawk Industries, Inc. is an Equal Opportunity Employer including disability/veteran committed to an inclusive workplace and a proud Drugs Don't Work participant. <br><br>Nearest Major Market: ColumbusApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjg4MzQ4LjEwNTA4QG1vaGF3a2luZHVzdHJpZXNjb21wLmFwbGl0cmFrLmNvbQ]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Engineering]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Katherine Bogue</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[Katherine_Bogue@mohawkind.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Production Associate (Dayton)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236157165]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-16]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236157165]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Hendrickson USA, L.L.C.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Dayton]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45402]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Terrific starting wages with step increases, and WE HELP PAY FOR YOUR COLLEGE EDUCATION!!<br><br>Hendrickson is looking for dedicated employees in our Composites Manufacturing operation as we continue to grow our Dayton, OH operations. COME JOIN OUR TEAM!!!<br><br>Positions open on Second and Third Shift. <br><br>Daily Responsibilities: <br><br>* Handle incoming and outgoing material to supply machines with material and tooling.<br>* Perform operations following processes defined by machine procedural manual.<br>* Operate production machines & equipment at or above minimum standards.<br>* Assure correctness of raw materials and inspection of parts.<br>* Packing <br><br>* Operator must be able to stand, bend, flex and lift <br>* Operator must be familiar with computers and the use of a hand scanner <br>* Attention to detail and good eye/hand coordination is required <br>* Ability to self-direct with good time management<br>* Complete required documentation as directed <br>* Effectively communicate issues to their Team Lead<br>* Adheres to Safety and Quality Standards <br><br>* Saw<br><br>* Operate pre-programmed Saw in an efficient manner<br>* Ensure Saw is producing correct parts<br>* Complete required documentation as directed <br>* Effectively communicate issues to their Team Lead<br>* Adheres to Safety and Quality Standards <br><br>* Satec<br><br>* Operates Satec Unit in efficient manner<br>* The Satec Operator is responsible for quality of all parts, as such, they must ensure issues are communicated effectively and efficiently <br>* Complete required documentation as directed <br>* Effectively communicate issues to their Team Lead<br>* Adheres to Safety and Quality Standards <br><br>* Sand<br><br>* Sands flashing from Springs as they are removed from the table <br>* Must be able to keep up with fast paced manufacturing environment while maintaining adherence to quality and safety <br>* Complete required documentation as directed <br>* Effectively communicate issues to their Team Lead<br>* Adheres to Safety and Quality Standards <br><br>* Huck and Pack <br><br>* Assemble Springs with specialized hardware as directed <br>* Operator must be able to bend and lift while carrying parts<br>* Complete required documentation as directed <br>* Effectively communicate issues to their Team Lead<br>* Adheres to Safety and Quality Standards <br><br>* All other duties as assigned<br><br>Qualifications:<br><br>* High school diploma or GED required<br>* Strong Attendance history<br>* Able to read and write legibly required<br>* Able to lift up to 40lb required<br>* Meet production-servicing standards required<br>Benefits:<br><br>* Medical, Dental and Vision<br>* 401K <br>* 100% Company paid Pension<br>* Generous Vacation Policy<br>* Paid Holidays<br>Hendrickson is an Equal Opportunity Employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability, or status as a protected veteran.<br><br>Additional Information<br><br>* Requisition ID: 2100015CApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjc1MDMxLjEwNTA4QGhlbmRyaWNrc29uY29tcC5hcGxpdHJhay5jb20]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Logistics/Transportation]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Marissa Tarasiuk</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[mtarasiuk@hendrickson-intl.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Quality Inspection/Final Test II (Ironton)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236162557]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-16]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236162557]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Vertiv Corporation]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Ironton]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45638]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[FOR INTERNAL EMPLOYEES ONLY, 1ST SHIFT, REPORTING TO RYAN JOHNSON, INTERNAL REQ NUMBER 2671<br><br>Position will perform functional testing of completed products. The position will be responsible for verifying conformance to all specified requirements. Duties Include, but are not limited to, physical inspection and functional inspection of electrical components, the operation of test bays/stations and associated equipment and troubleshooting and/or repairing faulty components. Position must assess product evaluation against NEC and UL/CSA standards. Review order write ups, operate components, ensure product quality, work with other areas to ensure product quality, and verify units to meet agency approvals. Other responsibilities as assigned. <br><br>* Uses basic hand tools such as ratchets, wrenches, air tools, pliers, wire stripper, torque tools, crimping tools <br>* Uses multi-meters <br>* Used hypot-tester <br>* Uses leak check equipment <br>* Uses computer <br>* Uses refrigeration manifold gauges <br><br>Vertiv is an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action employer. We promote equal opportunities for all with respect to hiring, terms of employment, mobility, training, compensation, and occupational health, without discrimination as to age, race, color, religion, creed, sex, pregnancy status (including childbirth, breastfeeding, or related medical conditions), marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity / expression (including transgender status or sexual stereotypes), genetic information, citizenship status, national origin, protected veteran status, political affiliation, or disability. If you have a disability and are having difficulty accessing or using this website to apply for a position, you can request help by sending an email to help.join@vertivco.com . <br><br>Work Authorization <br><br>No calls or agencies please. Vertiv will only employ those who are legally authorized to work in the United States. This is not a position for which sponsorship will be provided. Individuals with temporary visas such as E, F-1, H-1, H-2, L, B, J, or TN or who need sponsorship for work authorization now or in the future, are not eligible for hire.Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjY1Mjg5LjEwNTA4QHZlcnRpdmNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Engineering]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Elaina Lott</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[Elaina.Lott@vertiv.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Nurse Aide, $500 Sign-on Bonus (IJ, FT 1st shift ) STNA, $2,500 Sign-on Bonus (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236258347]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-18]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236258347]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION<br><br>The primary purpose of this position is to support the licensed staff by giving direct resident care and performing Nurse aide functions such as care for the personal needs and comfort of residents under the supervision of a Charge Nurse, and in accordance with current applicable federal, state and local standards, guidelines and regulations, Birchaven Village policy and procedure, Birchaven Village ethical statement and resident rights, subject to the employee handbook.<br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* High school diploma or equivalent training. <br>* Current registry with the State of Ohio Nurse Aide Registry or have completed Nurse Aide training with valid certificate within 4 months of hire. Or the 8 hour Nurse Aide program. Training can be provided. <br>PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Positive service-oriented interpersonal and communication skills required. <br>* Individual must be able to demonstrate the knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to needs of the residents served on his/her neighborhood. <br>* The individual must demonstrate basic knowledge of the principles related to the aging adult and problems associated with aging. <br>* Possess the ability to assess data reflective of the resident status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each residents needs. <br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS <br><br>This position requires a full range of body motion with intermittent activities in walking, sitting, lifting, bending, squatting, climbing, kneeling, twisting and standing. The associate will be required to lift 50 pounds or more. This position requires individuals to lift work above the shoulder. The associate must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. Individual must have excellent communication skills to perform daily tasks.<br><br>This position is classified at risk for possible occupational exposure to bloodborne pathogens (HBV, HIV etc.)<br><br>*BVHSApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjgyNDk4LjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Entry Level Security Officer (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236450138]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-21]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236450138]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheSecurity Officerposition helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjI2MzQ2LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Res Care Nurse, RN or LPN (FT 6a-6p) (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236456509]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-22]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236456509]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>RN- $5,000 Sign-on Bonus<br><br>LPN-$2,500 Sign-on Bonus<br><br>(Birchaven, C/D)<br><br>PURPOSE OF THE POSITION<br><br>The primary purpose of this position is to coordinate total nursing care for residents. Participates in resident and family teaching and provides leadership by working cooperatively in maintaining standards for professional nursing practice in a clinical setting and in accordance with current applicable federal, state and local standards, guidelines and regulations, policies and procedures, ethical statement and resident rights, subject to the employee handbook. <br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Graduate of an approved school of nursing. <br>* Current Ohio license for nursing. <br>PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Maximum exposure in regard to universal precautions. <br>* Positive service-oriented interpersonal and communication skills required. <br>* Individual must be able to demonstrate the knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to needs of the residents served on his/her neighborhood. <br>* The individual must demonstrate basic knowledge of the principles related to the aging adult and problems associated with aging. <br>* Possess the ability to assess data reflective of the resident status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each residents need. <br>* Provide care needed as directed by policy and procedure within the scope of an LPN/RN license. <br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS<br><br>This position requires a full range of body motion with intermittent walking, lifting, bending, climbing, squatting, kneeling, twisting, sitting and standing. This individual will be required to lift 50 pounds or more. This position requires individuals to lift work above the shoulders. Must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. This individual must have excellent verbal communication skills to perform daily tasks.<br><br>This position is classified at risk for possible occupational exposure to blood borne pathogens (HBV, HIV, etc.)Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjY0MDkxLjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Nurse Aide (Independence House, PT 2nd Shift) (Fostoria)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236599738]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-26]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236599738]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Fostoria]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44830]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>$2500 STNA Sign on Bonus<br><br>$500 Nurse Aide Sign on Bonus<br><br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION<br><br>The primary purpose of this position is to support the licensed staff by giving direct resident care and performing Nurse aide functions such as care for the personal needs and comfort of residents under the supervision of a Charge Nurse, and in accordance with current applicable federal, state and local standards, guidelines and regulations, Independence House policy and procedure, Independence Houseethical statement and resident rights, subject to the employee handbook.<br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Meet the minimum required age of 16 years old. <br>* Active State Tested Nurse Aide certification with the state of Ohio or have completed Nurse Aide training with certificate of completion. Or the 8 hour Nurse Aide program. Training can be provided. <br>PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Positive service-oriented interpersonal and communication skills required. <br>* Must be able to demonstrate the knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to needs of the residents served on his/her neighborhood. <br>* Must demonstrate basic knowledge of the principles related to the aging adult and problems associated with aging. <br>* Possess the ability to assess data reflective of the resident status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each residents needs. <br>PHYSICIAL DEMANDS<br><br>This position requires a full range of body motion with intermittent walking, lifting, bending, climbing, squatting, kneeling, twisting, sitting and standing. The associate will be required to lift 50 pounds or more. This position requires individuals to lift above the shoulders. The associate must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. The individual must have excellent verbal communications skills to perform daily tasks.<br><br>This position is classified at risk for possible occupational exposure to blood borne pathogens (HBV, HIV etc.)Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjkyMTE5LjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Private Duty Aide (Bridge PCS, FT, PT or PRN) (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236644994]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-28]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236644994]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>2nd and 3rd shift openings-Preferred<br><br>Must be available at least 12 weekend hours a month<br><br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION<br><br>The aide is responsible for the provision of personal care and homemaker services for clients in home settings. A plan of care, developed by a licensed nurse, will direct the services to be provided by the aide. The aide will work under the direction of the licensed nurse and the manager. <br><br>JOB DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES<br><br>Duty 1: Demonstrates knowledge and skill necessary to provide personal care appropriate to the age of the client and provides care in a consistent and timely manner.<br><br>Duty 2: Provides personal care within the scope of a certified nursing assistant and light housekeeping services as directed by the Nurse Coordinator and indicated on the Caregiver Assignment sheet in the client's home during every client visit.<br><br>Duty 3: Reports any changes in client's health and requests for additional services to the nurse coordinator or manager.<br><br>Duty 4: Logs into the current time keeping system using the client's telephone to record hours worked and services provided. Updates progress notes in the client's home and provides required documents to the office staff in timely manner.<br><br>Duty 5: Complies with organizational policies, procedures, and practices to ensure quality job performance and compliance.<br><br>Duty 6: Displays Service Excellence as evidenced by practicing the mission, vision and values of the organization to promote client satisfaction.<br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Must hold a current driver's license, with a clean drivingrecord. <br>PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Have completed a Nurse Aide training course or the equivalent. <br>* Positive service-oriented interpersonal and communication skills required. <br>* Individual must be able to demonstrate the knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patient served on his/her assigned unit/department. <br>* The individual must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to their age-specific needs and to provide the care needed as described in the area's policies and procedures. <br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS <br><br>This position requires a full range of body motion with intermittent walking, lifting, bending, climbing, squatting, kneeling, twisting, sitting, and standing. The associate will be required to walk up to 1 hour a day, sit for 4 hours a day, and stand for 2 hours a day. The individual must be able to lift 50 pounds and reach work above the shoulder. The individual must have good eye/hand coordination, and fine finger dexterity. This associate must have excellent verbal communication skills to perform daily tasks. The associate must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. <br><br>This position is classified at risk for possible occupational exposure to blood borne pathogens (HBV, HIV, etc.)<br><br>*BVHS<br>Job RequirementsApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjE5NzEzLjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Senior Platform Engineer (Youngstown)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236645426]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-28]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236645426]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Bucher & Christian Consulting, Inc.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Youngstown]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44503]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Senior Platform EngineerBCforward is currently seeking highly motivated Job Title in the location ! <br><br>Position Title: Cloud Engineer <br>Location: Youngstown, OH<br>Expected Duration (possible extension): 6+ Months CTH<br><br>Job Responsibilities <br><br>Position Description <br><br>* Expert in architecture disciplines<br>* Expert in architecture and design across all systems of the LOB<br>Skills:<br><br>* Create GitOps based event-driven high performance pipelines and tooling to fully automate the software delivery process.<br>* Work collaboratively with Banking developer communities.<br>* Bridge the gap between the development team and the Cloud platform team<br>* Great communication/collaboration skills<br>* Preferred Qualifications<br>* 5+ years of relevant software engineering experience<br>* Experience in open-source development<br>* Experience with Terraform<br>* Experience developing micro services<br>* Experience building and running large scale, multi-tenant distributed data systems<br>* Hands-on experience in managing life cycle of services on Kubernetes<br>* Experience in cloud environments such as GCP, AWS, Azure with container orchestration technology like Kubernetes<br>* Good knowledge of networking(HTTP, TLS, DNS) to troubleshoot network issues<br>* Proficiency in more than one programming language(C++, Java, Golang, Python)<br>* Strong understanding of concurrency, memory management and runtimes<br><br>About BCforward: <br><br>BCforward began as an IT business solution and staffing firm. Founded in 1998, BCforward has grown with our customers' needs into a full-service personnel solutions organization. Headquartered in Indianapolis, Indiana, BCforward also operates numerous delivery centers across North America and India. We are currently the largest consulting firm and largest MBE certified firm in Indiana. Our uninterrupted growth has allowed BCforward to deliver uniquely configured IT staffing and project solutions for over years of catering to our customers' specific needs. BCforward currently maintains a team of over 5000 global resources. With our additional brand, Stafforward, together we have the capabilities to deliver services for a variety of industries in both public and private sectors which allows us to address your most challenging needs. <br>www.BCforward.com <br><br>www.facebook.com/bcforward <br>This posting is not an offer of employment. All applicants must be authorized to work in the United States and willing cooperate with a background check and drug screen, to the extent permitted by federal and local laws up to, and including, both criminal and financial reviews. The submission of intentionally false or fraudulent information in response to this job posting shall render the applicant ineligible for the position. BCforward is an equal opportunity employer. Any subsequent offer of employment shall be considered employment at will regardless of the anticipated assignment duration. <br><br>Interested candidates please send resume in Word format Please reference job code 150649 when responding to this ad.<br><br>Recommended Skills<br><br>* Amazon Web Services<br>* Architecture<br>* Automation<br>* C++ (Programming Language)<br>* Cloud Platform System<br>* Dns<br><br>Get job alerts by email.Sign up now!Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjc2Mzc2LjEwNTA4QGJjZm9yd2FyZGNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[IT/Software Development]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Jacob Pruis</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[Compliance@bcforward.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Res Care Nurse (EF) (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236718173]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-29]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236718173]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>PURPOSE OF THE POSITION<br><br>The primary purpose of this position is to coordinate total nursing care for residents. Participates in resident and family teaching and provides leadership by working cooperatively in maintaining standards for professional nursing practice in a clinical setting and in accordance with current applicable federal, state and local standards, guidelines and regulations, policies and procedures, ethical statement and resident rights, subject to the employee handbook. <br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Graduate of an approved school of nursing. <br>* Current Ohio license for nursing. <br>PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Maximum exposure in regard to universal precautions. <br>* Positive service-oriented interpersonal and communication skills required. <br>* Individual must be able to demonstrate the knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to needs of the residents served on his/her neighborhood. <br>* The individual must demonstrate basic knowledge of the principles related to the aging adult and problems associated with aging. <br>* Possess the ability to assess data reflective of the resident status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each residents need. <br>* Provide care needed as directed by policy and procedure within the scope of an LPN/RN license. <br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS<br><br>This position requires a full range of body motion with intermittent walking, lifting, bending, climbing, squatting, kneeling, twisting, sitting and standing. This individual will be required to lift 50 pounds or more. This position requires individuals to lift work above the shoulders. Must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. This individual must have excellent verbal communication skills to perform daily tasks.<br><br>This position is classified at risk for possible occupational exposure to blood borne pathogens (HBV, HIV, etc.)Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjA5MzAzLjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Nurse Aide (H) (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236718184]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-29]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236718184]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION<br><br>The primary purpose of this position is to support the licensed staff by giving direct resident care and performing Nurse aide functions such as care for the personal needs and comfort of residents under the supervision of a Charge Nurse, and in accordance with current applicable federal, state and local standards, guidelines and regulations, Birchaven Village policy and procedure, Birchaven Village ethical statement and resident rights, subject to the employee handbook.<br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* High school diploma or equivalent training. <br>* Current registry with the State of Ohio Nurse Aide Registry or have completed Nurse Aide training with valid certificate within 4 months of hire <br>PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Positive service-oriented interpersonal and communication skills required. <br>* Individual must be able to demonstrate the knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to needs of the residents served on his/her neighborhood. <br>* The individual must demonstrate basic knowledge of the principles related to the aging adult and problems associated with aging. <br>* Possess the ability to assess data reflective of the resident status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each residents needs. <br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS <br><br>This position requires a full range of body motion with intermittent activities in walking, sitting, lifting, bending, squatting, climbing, kneeling, twisting and standing. The associate will be required to lift 50 pounds or more. This position requires individuals to lift work above the Shoulder. The associate must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. Individual must have excellent verbal communication skills to perform daily tasks. <br><br>This position is classified at risk for possible occupational exposure to bloodborne pathogens (HBV, HIV etc.)Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjg3MTA1LjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[.NET Developer (Columbus)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237047775]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-08]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237047775]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Bucher & Christian Consulting, Inc.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Columbus]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[43215]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[.NET DeveloperPosition Title: .NET Developer<br>Location: Columbus, OH<br>Expected Duration: 12 Months contract to hire.<br><br>Responsibilities include:<br><br>* Expert in in .NET design technique as well as experience working across large environments with multiple operating systems/infrastructure for large-scale programs<br><br>* multi-skilled with expertise across software development lifecycle and toolset<br><br>* Services provided by these resources will be dedicated to providing application development and support during the United States daytime hours.<br>* &sect; Sought out as coach for at least one technical skill<br>&sect; Strong understanding of techniques such as Continuous Integration, Continuous Delivery, Test<br>Driven Development, Cloud Development, resiliency, security<br><br>Interested candidates please send resume in Word format Please reference job code 161433 when responding to this ad.<br><br>Recommended Skills<br><br>* Coaching And Mentoring<br>* Continuous Delivery<br>* Continuous Integration<br>* Infrastructure Management<br>* Multitasking<br>* Operational Systems<br><br>Get job alerts by email.Sign up now!Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjA4NjU1LjEwNTA4QGJjZm9yd2FyZGNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[IT/Software Development]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Jacob Pruis</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[Compliance@bcforward.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Welder - 1st Shift (Lebanon)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237056813]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-08]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237056813]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[FECON, Inc.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Lebanon]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45036]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Title: Welder <br><br>Manager Title: Production Supervisor <br><br>FLSA Status: Non-Exempt <br><br>FECON, LLC is a vegetation management equipment manufacturer located in Lebanon, Ohio near Kings Island Amusement Park. FECON is known for having very high-quality products and a team culture - and we are growing! We design, build, test, sell and service our equipment consisting of products such as our well-known "Bull Hog" mulchers, the Stump Ex, our high-quality FTX tractors of varying horsepower, as well as many other attachments. We offer competitive wages, full health care benefits and a continuous learning culture for those who want to grow with the company.<br><br>Job Summary:<br><br>Welds and assembles metal pieces and products by using handheld welding equipment. Sets up parts for welding; uses hand tools, clamps, jigs and fixtures. Works from specifications, drawings and weld symbols. Prepares and completes work on materials by welding, cutting, grinding and cleaning metal.<br><br>Job Duties/Responsibilities:<br><br>* Follows all FECON safety programs and requirements.<br>* Adheres to production schedule.<br>* Reads, assembles, and welds from blueprints.<br>* Prepares, assembles, and tacks weld parts and surfaces to be welded.<br>* Monitors the welding, burning, and fitting process to ensure parts are not overheated or damaged by warping, distortion, expansion, or shrinkage.<br>* GMAW/MIG Spray Transfer welding. Settings up to 250 Amp, 32 Volt, 400 IPM wire speed.<br>* 1G, 2G and 3G welding daily.<br>* Uses .045 - .052 metal core wire using 90/10 gas.<br>* Grinds and wire wheels product to clean smooth surfaces for painting.<br>* Inspects final products to print for quality assurance.<br>* Tags all final products for identification.<br>* Maintains, organizes, and cleans equipment and the work area.<br>* Operates overhead and jib style crane.<br>* Operates a forklift.<br>* Notifies supervisor when faulty equipment or defective materials are discovered.<br>* Performs other related duties as assigned.<br>Required Skills/Abilities:<br><br>* Training and experience in GMAW/MIG and FCAW welding is required.<br>* Thorough understanding of machines and tools used in welding.<br>* Ability to read weld symbols and follow blueprints.<br>* Excellent ability to read and listen to assignments given in a variety of forms.<br>* Basic understanding of mathematics as related to welding assignments.<br>* Must be able to weld components that are vertical, flat, or overhead.<br>* Must have enough manual dexterity and stability as required for precision work.<br>Education and Experience: <br><br>* High school or equivalent<br>* Minimum of 2 years solid welding experience required.<br>Physical Requirements:<br><br>* Ability to safely use and lift equipment weighing 50 pounds. <br>* Ability to work standing up to 10 hours per day.<br><br>This job description is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities that are required of the employee. Duties, responsibilities and activities may change or new ones may be added at any time with or without notice.<br><br>Benefit and Company Information:<br><br>* Medical, Dental, Vision and Life Insurance<br>* 401k Participation<br>* Short-Term and Long-Term Disability Insurance<br>* Vacation and Paid Holidays<br>* Education Assistance<br>* Compensation based on experience.<br>* This position is hourly, non-exempt.<br>* This is a first shift position. Hours for this position are 5:30a - 4:00p, Monday-Thursday. Some overtime is required. <br><br>Equal Opportunity Employer/Veterans/DisabledApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjkwMDg5LjEwNTA4QGZlY29uY29tcC5hcGxpdHJhay5jb20]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Engineering]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Megan Cunningham</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[mcunningham@fecon.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[System Support Administrator (Springfield)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237179102]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-10]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237179102]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[MAG DS Corp]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Springfield]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45501]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Position Summary<br><br>MAG Aerospace is looking to hire a Sr System Administrator to support our ANG RPA SOC customer's project out of Springfield, OH.<br>Essential Duties and Responsibilities<br><br>* Primary responsibilities are to maintain the (POC) in an operational ready state and assist operations teams with solutions to real time issues, both computer and communications and assist customer to: define, document, and integrate required computer, communications and intelligence capabilities to enhance UAV and POC missions. <br>* Systems monitored include: NIPRNet, SIPRNet, JWICS, internal/external voice communications system(s), VoIP, NSTS phone system, Video Teleconferencing Center, and video dissemination.<br>Requirements<br><br>The position is contingent upon candidate's ability to meet physical and medical requirements as needed by the position; thereby, including compliance with all applicable federal, state, and local jurisdictional requirements with respect to COVID-19, as well as any Government or customer site-specific requirements. Requirements typically include but are not limited to proof of full COVID-19 vaccination status, except in circumstances where a candidate is legally entitled to an accommodation.<br><br>* Military C4ISR (Command, Control, Computers, Communication, Intelligence, Surveillance, and Reconnaissance) systems experience <br>* Experience with Windows 7 and Server 2008 administration <br>* Microsoft Internet Information Server (IIS) and Domain Name System (DNS) in a mixed Window/Unix environment <br>* Familiarly with UNIX or LINUX as a user <br>* Hardware maintenance and installation <br>* Experience with basic email and office administration software i.e. Microsoft Office set-up and maintenance. (This is not an exhaustive list as there may be other software required) <br>* One or more of the following systems: SAN Storage, Server Blade, SQL, SharePoint, C2ISR video data, network performance software <br>* Active US Top Secret/SCI <br>* Must possess DOD 8570 IAT II level certification <br>* A+ and/or Network+ <br>* Minimum of a High School Degree with at least 4 years of direct relevant work experience <br>* Must hold one of the following certifications within employment: VMware 6, CCNA and MCSA <br><br>Preferred but NOT Required Education and Experience (education that is not necessary but will make a candidate more qualified for the position)<br><br>* US Air Force (or other military) experience in a computer - related discipline is highly desired.<br><br>* Operational experience with UAV's.<br><br>* Familiarity with DOD cryptographic equipment.<br><br>* Prior military or civilian DOD experience with Air Operations is highly desired<br><br>* Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, IT, or Engineering<br><br>#LI-WN1<br><br>Company Policy<br><br>MAG Aerospace (MAG) is an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer and is committed to Diversity and Inclusion. We encourage diverse candidates to apply to our positions.All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability, or veteran status.Click below for the "EEO is The Law" and "Pay Transparency Nondiscrimination" supplement posters.<br><br>https://www.dol.gov/agencies/ofccp/posters<br><br>MAG Aerospace (MAG) is committed to providing an online application process that is accessible to all, including individuals with a disability, by offering an alternative way to apply for job openings. This alternative method is available for those who cannot otherwise complete the online application due to a disability or need for accommodation.MAG provides reasonable accommodation to applicants under the guidance of the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjM1MTgyLjEwNTA4QG1hZ2Flcm9zcGFjZWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Engineering]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Nedra Brown</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[MAG.co@localjobnetwork.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer-Advanced (Columbus)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237180885]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-10]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237180885]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Bucher & Christian Consulting, Inc.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Columbus]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[43215]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer-Advanced<br>BCforward is currently seeking highly motivated Software Engineering - Software Engineering- Full stack developer-Advanced for Texas.<br><br>Position Title: Software Engineering - Full stack developer-Advanced .<br>Location: Columbus, Ohio.<br>Expected Duration: 6 Months Contract to Hire.<br><br>Job Description<br><br>* Expert in in Full Stack design technique as well as experience working across large environments with multiple operating systems/infrastructure for large-scale programs (e.g., Expert Engineers) starting to be firm-wide resources working on projects across JPMC<br>* Is multi-skilled with expertise across software development lifecycle and toolset<br>* May be recognized as a leader in Agile and cultivating teams working in Agile frameworks<br>* Sought out as coach for at least one technical skill<br>* Strong understanding of techniques such as Continuous Integration, Continuous Delivery, TestDriven Development, Cloud Development, resiliency, security<br>* Stays abreast of cutting edge technologies/trends and uses experience to influence application of those technologies/trends to support the business; may give speeches and outside the firm, writes articles<br><br>Core Responsibilities<br><br>* Candidates should have 7 to 10 years experience. They should have previous leadership experience and will to be a scrum lead for a scrum team. They should have knowledge in the following areas:<br>* Java 8 or higher<br>* Spring Framework<br>* Microservices<br>* API<br>* Kafka Event Driven Design<br>* The should be a team player that possesses leadership skills. They should be familiar with Agile methodology. The need to have an willingness to learn and teach. The should have an outgoing personality and great communication skills<br>* This role requires a wide variety of strengths and capabilities, including:<br>* Advanced knowledge of application, data and infrastructure architecture disciplines, understanding of architecture and design across all systems proficiency in developmental toolsets.<br>* Ability to collaborate with high-performing teams and individuals throughout the firm to accomplish common goals. High performing individual contributor, responsible to maintain business critical platforms and deliver high ROI business features.<br>* Build expertise in the team and position for a platform re-engineering program<br>* Understand the architecture of the existing applications and develop features solutions for the full stack; UI, Java-based back-end, database and messaging<br>* Apply latest Dev Ops concepts to continuously improve and transform platform into a highly available, highly maintainable platform - including but not limited to code, policy, processes, and tools. Improve monitoring, automated validation and synthetic transactions, collaboration between Dev and Ops and automated SDLC tool chain.<br>* Work collaboratively in an Agile Feature team setup with team members located across different locations and time zones. Contribute to delivery success across teams as a technology coach and lead developer.<br>* Have a strong focus on time and resource-management, decision-making and ability to operate with parallel project deliveries.<br>* Monitor production activities/processes to ensure timely and effective reporting, tracking, f<br><br>About BCforward: <br>BCforward began as an IT business solutions and staffing firm. Founded in 1998, BCforward has grown with our customers' needs into a full service personnel solutions organization. Headquartered in Indianapolis, Indiana, BCforward also operates numerous delivery centers across North America and India. We are currently the largest consulting firm and largest MBE certified firm in Indiana. Our uninterrupted growth has allowed BCforward to deliver uniquely confApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjEzMzYxLjEwNTA4QGJjZm9yd2FyZGNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[IT/Software Development]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Jacob Pruis</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[Compliance@bcforward.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Manufacturing Facility Security Officer - $14.92/hour (Urbana)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237276499]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237276499]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Urbana]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[43078]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheSecurity Officerposition helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjUxMDQ1LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Product Cost Manager (Sandusky)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237276962]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237276962]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[John Bean Technologies Corporation]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Sandusky]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44870]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<STRONG>JBT Corporation</STRONG><br><br>AN EQUAL OPPORTUNITY EMPLOYER<br><br>It is the policy of JBT Corporation to provide equal opportunity for qualified persons and not to discriminate against any applicant for employment because of race, color, religion, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, disability, veteran status, citizenship, or any other characteristic protected by federal, state or local law at the JBT Corporation location to which this application is submitted. In addition, as a Federal Government contractor, JBT Corporation is an affirmative action employer. If you require accommodation during the application process, please contact the local Human Resources department. EOE-Females/Minorities/Protected Veterans/Individuals with Disabilities<br><br>If you have a disability or impairment that prevents you from completing the online application, please seek the assistance of your local employment services agency. JBT maintains active relationships with local employment services agencies, and they have pledged their support in assisting any applicant needing help in applying. To find information on agencies throughout the United States, please go to www.careeronestop.org<br><br>You may also call Megan Meagrow at 844-286-4524 if your disability or impairment prevents you from applying online. NOTE: Do not use this number unless you need assistance because of a disability or impairment. The personnel attending this phone line will not be able to give you a status update regarding your application and will not be the individuals making a decision regarding your employment.<br><br><STRONG>Product Cost Manager</STRONG><br><br>US-OH-Sandusky<br><br><STRONG>Job ID:</STRONG> 2022-8570<br><STRONG>Type:</STRONG> Regular Full-Time<br><STRONG># of Openings:</STRONG> 1<br><STRONG>Category:</STRONG> Product Development<br><br>JBT Corporation<br><br><STRONG>Overview</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>Overview </STRONG><br><br>JBT is a diverse, global company with many needs for international management talent and great opportunities for experienced graduates Our businesses are worldwide and opportunities are broad in scope<br><br><STRONG>Start your career with us</STRONG><br><br>Being a global company allows us to present you with a number of career opportunities JBT is one of the largest solutions providers to the global food processing industry The largest food processors within the fruit, vegetable, meat, poultry, seafood and bakery industries are among our customers<br><br><STRONG>BENEFITS - </STRONG><STRONG> Start from day 1! </STRONG><br><br>JBT Corporation offers the growth potential of a company with a developing technology that is unique in its field, plus frequent company-sponsored events and a competitive benefits package that includes:<br><UL><LI>Medical, Dental, Vision coverage</LI><LI>401(k) plan with company match - up to 65%</LI><LI>Company paid Short Term Disability, Long Term Disability, and Life Insurance</LI><LI>Paid Parental Leave</LI><LI>Paid Holidays</LI><LI>Vacation pay</LI><LI>Sick pay</LI><LI>Annual Bonus Pay</LI><LI>Tuition Reimbursement (*eligible after 2 years)</LI></UL><br><br><STRONG>Responsibilities</STRONG><br><br><STRONG> JOB SUMMARY </STRONG><STRONG>: </STRONG><br> <br>This position is responsible for the ownership and maintaining all costing tools for the Coating, Frying, Cooking, and Freezing Product Lines manufactured in Sandusky, OH including providing budgetary assistance to the front end team<br><br>This position is expected to work closely with applications, project managers, purchasing department, product line manager(s), engineers, and sales coordinators to ensure that the costing tools are accurate and reflect typical market requests for quote (RFQ) Additionally, this position will work closely with Purchasing, Allied Suppliers and Strategic Partners to ensure supplier price lists are readily available and updated for large ticket purchased items such as coils, radiators, conveyors, TF Heaters, etc<br><br>This position will travel up to 10% of the time Travel includes trips between JBT locations in Northfield, MN, Redmond, WA, Sandusky, OH, Alpharetta, GA, Edinburgh, Scotland, and Helsingborg, Sweden Travel also includes visits to supplier locations around the United States and Canada<br><br><STRONG> ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES: </STRONG><br><br> To perform this job successfully, an individual must be able to perform each essential duty satisfactorily The requirements listed below are representative of the knowledge, skill and/or ability required Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions Frequency of duties, percent of time and work year may vary based on department or building assignment <br><br><UL><LI>Solely responsible for maintaining reliable tools for generating fast budget estimates for the Coating, Frying, Cooking, and Freezing Product Lines manufactured in Sandusky, OH</LI><LI>Responsible for analyzing closed order variance (COV) and establishing non-conformance amounts by product line / project and feeding this information back to departments for appropriate mitigation</LI><LI>Gatekeeper responsible for adjusting project budgets from budgeted allowance</LI><LI>The Cost List Manager is NOT responsible for managing towards achieving/beating a budget nor will she or he be responsible for providing forecasts for ongoing projects relative to budget</LI><LI>Actively participate in post project review meetings and decide when adjusting budgeted costs (based on actual costs incurred on a project/order) should be made</LI><LI>Work closely with the Engineering and Operations teams to provide advice on large ticket items / costs that are directly prohibiting sales</LI><LI>The Cost List Manager will be responsible for screening and responding to all sales coordinator generated requests in a timely fashion</LI><LI>Expected to estimate costs for the purposes of quick quote turnaround when quotes/price lists for particular materials/equipment options are not readily available</LI><LI>Utilize engineering, purchasing, and applications as needed to maintain budget tools</LI><LI>Will track budgeted costs for major product lines year over year and report findings yearly to senior management</LI><LI>Expected to work intimately w/ Product Line Management to ensure that the costing tools match the current equipment/market standards</LI><LI>Additional responsibilities to be assigned as needed</LI></UL><br><br><STRONG>Qualifications</STRONG><br><br>Successful applicants must be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment Vaccine verification will be required upon acceptance of employment <br><br><STRONG> EDUCATION & EXPERIENCE: </STRONG><br><UL><LI>Bachelor&rsquo;s degree in related field required</LI><LI>Minimum of 5 years&rsquo; applicable industry related experience</LI></UL><br><br><STRONG> KNOWLEDGE AND SKILLS: </STRONG><br><UL><LI>Highly developed organizational skills with the ability to handle multiple tasks and thrive in a change-oriented, fast-paced, high stress environment where schedules, deadlines, and customer demands can shift priorities</LI></UL><UL><LI>Strong oral and written communications skills with all levels of employees and customers</LI><LI>Computer skill expertise in spreadsheet, word processing, relational database, presentation, and MS Outlook software applications required</LI><LI>A working knowledge of ERP (SyteLine) business system software a plus</LI></UL><UL><LI>Knowledge of high-volume portioning, coating, frying, cooking, freezing, and refrigeration equipment and processes a plus, but not required</LI><LI>Ability to work w/ minimal supervision on tedious cost development tools</LI></UL><br><br><STRONG> WORK ENVIRONMENT AND PHYSICAL DEMANDS: </STRONG> Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform essential functions <br><br><STRONG>Work Environment: </STRONG><br><br>Office/meeting and manufacturing shop environment Exposed to possible shop hazards including heavy equipment, shop traffic, uneven/slippery footing, inclement weather, etc Production shop requires appropriate safety measures such as safety shoes and safety glasses<br><br><STRONG>Physical Demands: </STRONG><br><br>Moderate physical demands that include frequent walking, and some bending or climbing Fast paced environment with multiple priorities, constant change and a variety of problems and people involved<br><br>This job description is a summary of essential job functions It is not intended as an employment contract, nor is it intended to describe all duties someone in this position may perform All employees are expected to perform tasks as assigned by supervisor, regardless of job title or routine job duties<br><br>You may also call (844) 286-4524 if your disability or impairment prevents you from applying online NOTE: Do not use this number unless you need assistance because of a disability or i <br><br>Apply Here <br><br>PI164759556]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Other]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Luisa Hernandez</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[jt.sjb@jobtarget.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Audiologist - Medical Practice/Specialty (ENT) - Full-Time (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237277048]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237277048]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION<br><br>The purpose of the is position is to perform audio-logical evaluations for pediatric and adult patients, perform electro-physiologic evaluations, including infant and adult ABRs and ECOGs, perform VNG evaluations, and tp administer adult and pediatric hearing aid fittings and counsel on maintenance of hearing aids.<br><br>JOB DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES<br><br>Duty 1: Performs comprehensive audio-logical evaluations of both pediatric and adult patients.<br><br>Duty 2: Performs electro-physiologic evaluations (ABR and ECOG).<br><br>Duty 3: Perform VNG evaluations.<br><br>Duty 4: Administers hearing aid fittings and provides counseling for both pediatric and adult patients.<br><br>Duty 5: Completes charting on test results and recommendations.<br><br>Duty 6: Provides patients with recommendations and/or referrals as needed.<br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Licensed audiologist in the state of Ohio. <br>* Ability to learn and be proficient with Cerner EMR. <br>* Ability to collaborate with ENT physicians within the practice in caring for mutual patients. <br>* Positive service-oriented interpersonal and communication (written and verbal) skills required. <br>* Individual must be able to demonstrate the knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patient served on his/her assigned unit/department. The individual must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient status. Must be able to interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to their age-specific needs and to provide the care needed as described in the area's policies and procedures. <br>PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Experience with diagnostic infant ABR/OAE evaluations. <br>* Experience with VNG evaluations. <br>* Experience with hearing aid fitting/counseling. <br>* Experience with cochlear implants. <br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS<br><br>This position requires a full range of body motion with intermittent walking, lifting, bending, squatting, kneeling, twisting and standing. The associate will be required to walk for up to one hour a day, sit continuously for six hours a day and stand for one hour a day. The individual must be able to lift twenty to fifty pounds and reach work above the shoulders. The individual must have good eye-hand coordination and fine finger dexterity for simple grasping tasks. The individual must have excellent verbal communication skills to perform daily tasks. The associate must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. The individual must be able to operate a motor vehicle for business travel and community involvement.<br><br>This position is classified "at risk" for possible occupational exposure to blood borne pathogens (HBV, HIV, etc.)<br><br>*BVHSApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjA1OTQ4LjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Project Manager (Sandusky)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237182886]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-10]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237182886]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[John Bean Technologies Corporation]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Sandusky]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44870]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<STRONG>JBT Corporation</STRONG><br><br>AN EQUAL OPPORTUNITY EMPLOYER<br><br>It is the policy of JBT Corporation to provide equal opportunity for qualified persons and not to discriminate against any applicant for employment because of race, color, religion, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, disability, veteran status, citizenship, or any other characteristic protected by federal, state or local law at the JBT Corporation location to which this application is submitted. In addition, as a Federal Government contractor, JBT Corporation is an affirmative action employer. If you require accommodation during the application process, please contact the local Human Resources department. EOE-Females/Minorities/Protected Veterans/Individuals with Disabilities<br><br>If you have a disability or impairment that prevents you from completing the online application, please seek the assistance of your local employment services agency. JBT maintains active relationships with local employment services agencies, and they have pledged their support in assisting any applicant needing help in applying. To find information on agencies throughout the United States, please go to www.careeronestop.org<br><br>You may also call Megan Meagrow at 844-286-4524 if your disability or impairment prevents you from applying online. NOTE: Do not use this number unless you need assistance because of a disability or impairment. The personnel attending this phone line will not be able to give you a status update regarding your application and will not be the individuals making a decision regarding your employment.<br><br><STRONG>Project Manager</STRONG><br><br>US-OH-Sandusky<br><br><STRONG>Job ID:</STRONG> 2022-8520<br><STRONG>Type:</STRONG> Regular Full-Time<br><STRONG># of Openings:</STRONG> 2<br><STRONG>Category:</STRONG> Project Management<br><br>JBT Corporation<br><br><STRONG>Overview</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>Overview </STRONG><br><br>JBT is a diverse, global company with many needs for international management talent and great opportunities for experienced graduates Our businesses are worldwide and opportunities are broad in scope<br><br><STRONG>Start your career with us</STRONG><br><br>Being a global company allows us to present you with a number of career opportunities JBT is one of the largest solutions providers to the global food processing industry The largest food processors within the fruit, vegetable, meat, poultry, seafood and bakery industries are among our customers<br><br><STRONG>BENEFITS - </STRONG><STRONG> Start from day 1! </STRONG><br><br>JBT Corporation offers the growth potential of a company with a developing technology that is unique in its field, plus frequent company-sponsored events and a competitive benefits package that includes:<br><UL><LI>Medical, Dental, Vision coverage</LI><LI>401(k) plan with company match - up to 65%</LI><LI>Company paid Short Term Disability, Long Term Disability, and Life Insurance</LI><LI>Paid Parental Leave</LI><LI>Paid Holidays</LI><LI>Vacation pay</LI><LI>Sick pay</LI><LI>Tuition Reimbursement (*eligible after 2 years)</LI></UL><br><br><STRONG>Responsibilities</STRONG><br><br>Plans and manages multiple projects including the coordination of materials and personnel: in-house, with suppliers, and on-site at customer locations Manages the detailed technical schedule and financial performance of the project to deliver a quality product, on time, and within the project budget Serves as the primary internal point of contact for Customers, Sales, Service, Manufacturing, Purchasing, and Engineering for the entire life cycle of the project<br><br>Receives direction from manager to set broad objectives Consistently and clearly demonstrates creativity and innovation in finding solutions to multi-faceted problems Meets quality requirements without sacrificing safety, cost and delivery goals Works with various departments to recommend methods to control job cost and non-conformances Must be willing to travel to site to assist with high-risk project pre-installation meetings and active installations<br><br><STRONG> ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES : </STRONG><br><br> To perform this job successfully, an individual must be able to perform each essential duty satisfactorily The requirements listed below are representative of the knowledge, skill and/or ability required Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions Frequency of duties, percent of time and work year may vary based on department or building assignment <br><br>Actively participate in established proposal/budget review meetings (with PLM/Sales and other business departments) to identify possible hazards/risks of a project in the quotation stage to help ensure booked gross margins are achieved When necessary will help Apps/Sales with proposal writing/budgeting/drawings and Pre-Sale customer visits<br> <br>20%<br> <br>Serves as the primary point of contact between JBT and the customer upon Order Entry Manages customer expectations with respect to scope of work, project schedule, and buyer/seller responsibilities Confirms customer&rsquo;s agreement/completion of their mechanical and production start-up responsibilities Builds and maintains a positive relationship with customers and suppliers associated with the project<br> <br>20%<br> <br>Develops and manages project schedules to ensure on-time completion of the contractually required project milestones including final delivery of equipment, installation, mechanical start-up, and production start-up Participate in onsite customer kick-off meetings and pre-installation meeting for all high-risk projects to help mitigate any further risks and ensure the customer has all necessary information to perform a successful project<br> <br>20%<br> <br>Participates onsite in the active install of any assigned High-Risk project Resolves field installation problems by maintaining close contact with customers, sales account managers, and field personnel Responsible for managing and communicating the active punch list of issues during a project installation phase Coordinates timely corrective action with internal and external resources while minimizing cost impact to the project<br> <br>20%<br> <br>Ensure that Project cost tracking and forecasted spending are updated in the business systems accurately and on a timely basis Provide monthly forecast of expected project completion, costs, COV and final gross margin Setup a postmortem review of all high-risk projects, evaluate all task margins/issues and create and implement long term corrective actions plans via MRR process<br> <br>20%<br><br><STRONG>Occasional Responsibilities:</STRONG><br><br>Performs other duties as assigned by Senior Manager, Project Execution<br><br><STRONG>Qualifications</STRONG><br><br>Successful applicants must be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment Vaccine verification will be required upon acceptance of employment <br><br><STRONG>EXPERIENCE AND EDUCATION:<br></STRONG>&bull; BS Degree in related field required<br>&bull; PMP Certification preferred<br>&bull; Minimum 3 years&rsquo; experience with Project Management in a capital equipment environment<br>&bull; Must have experience in supplier/procurement processes<br><br><STRONG>TECHNICAL SKILLS, KNOWLEDGE & ABILITIES</STRONG><br><br>&bull; Technical background in manufacturing, fabrication, construction, and service disciplines preferred<br><br>&bull; Understand process flow charts<br><br>&bull; Design of experiments methodology<br>&bull; Ability to read and interpret engineering and assembly drawings<br>&bull; Ability to develop, monitor, analyze, and control project budgets<br>&bull; General knowledge of mechanical utility services<br>&bull; Knowledge of high-volume portioning, coating, frying, cooking, freezing, and refrigeration equipment and processes a plus<br>&bull; Highly developed organizational skills with the ability to handle multiple tasks and thrive in a change-oriented, fast-paced, high stress environment where schedules, deadlines, and customer demands can shift priorities <br>&bull; Strong interpersonal skills and ability to effectively interface with co-workers, customers, and suppliers <br>&bull; Strong analytical problem solving/root cause analysis techniques along with preventive and corrective action skills<br>&bull; Strong reporting and presentation skills <br>&bull; Strong negotiating, planning, verbal and written communications skills<br><br><STRONG>PLATFORM, DATABASE AND EQUIPMENT OPERATING KNOWLEDGE:</STRONG><br>&bull; Fluent in AutoCAD as is required to develop equipment layouts or proposal drawings<br>&bull; A working knowledge of ERP (SyteLine) business system software a plus<br>&bull; Computer skill expertise in spreadsheet, word processing, MS Project, relational database, presentation, project management, and MS Outlook software applications required<br><br><STRONG>REPORTING RELATIONSHIPS & DIRECTION/GUIDANCE:</STRONG><br><br>&bull; This position reports to: Senior Manager, Project Execution<br>&bull; Field Technicians on a dotted line basis during equipment installation and start-up activities and Site Crew on a direct basis during the equipment build and installation process, as appropriate<br><br><STRONG>FINANCIAL RESPONSIBILITY:</STRONG><br><br>&bull; Project sales value averages $10 million each<br>&bull; Manages approximately 5-15 projects at any given time<br><br><STRONG> PHYSICAL REQUIREMENTS & WORKING CONDITIONS : </STRONG> The physical demands, work environment factors and mental functions described below are representative of those that must be met by an employee to successfully perform the essential functions of this job Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions <br><br>Must be willing to travel to site (US/Mexico/Canada) to assist with high-risk project pre-installation meetings and active installations Estimate 60-70% of time in an office or meeting environment Exposed to possible shop or site installation hazards including heavy equipment, shop traffic, uneven/slippery footing, inclement weather, etc Sites environments are typically indoor, wet, 30-40 refrigerated rooms Installation sites require appropriate JBT and Customer set safety attire such as hard hat, Steel Toe Shoes, safety glasses, hair nets, lab coats, gloves (NO JEWELRY of any kind)<br><br>Frequent sitting and operating computer Frequent walking and standing Spends approximately 30-40% of time in a field environment to meet with customers, suppliers, account managers, field technicians, etc to monitor and manage project scope, site conditions, schedule, cost, etc and to resolve critical supplier or installation site problems Fast paced environment with multiple priorities, constant change and a variety of problems and people involved<br><br>This job description is a summary of essential job functions It is not intended as an employment contract, nor is it intended to describe all duties someone in this position may perform All employees are expected to perform tasks as assigned by supervisor, regardless of job title or routine job duties<br><br>You may also call Susan Cotton at 844-286-4524 if your disability or impairment prevents you from applying online NOTE: Do not use this number unless you need assistance because of a disability or i<br><br>Apply Here <br><br>PI164629888]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Project/Program Management]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Luisa Hernandez</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[jt.sjb@jobtarget.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Security Guard (Bellevue)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237277296]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237277296]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Bellevue]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44811]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheSecurity Officerposition helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjc0NDM4LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Security/Protective Services]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Supply Chain Coordinator (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237277657]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237277657]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br><br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION <br><br>The primary purpose of the Supply Chain Coordinator position is to provide flexibility and ensure quality outcomes with the basic supply chain functions. This position will have the skills and ability to work in all front line positions including but not limited to the Storeroom Coordinator position, the Purchasing Coordinator position, the Receiving Coordinator position, basic Buyer position functions, and basic Inventory Control Coordinator functions.<br><br>JOB FUNCTIONS<br><br>Every effort has been made to make this job description as complete as possible. However, it in no way states or implies that these are the only duties you will be required to perform. The omission of specific statements of duties does not exclude them from the position if the work is similar, related or a logical assignment.<br><br>JOB DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES<br><br>* Duty 1: Ability to perform all functions of the Storeroom Coordinator position and provides coverage for that position as needed. <br>* Duty 2: Ability to perform all functions of the Purchasing Coordinator position and provides coverage for that position as needed. <br>* Duty 3: Ability to perform all functions of the Receiving Coordinator position and provides coverage for that position as needed. <br>* Duty 4: Ability to perform basic Buyer position functions and provides coverage for that position as needed. <br>* Duty 5: Ability to perform basic Inventory Control Coordinator functions and provides coverage for that position as needed. <br>* Duty 6: Acts as role model and mentor for all supply chain associates. Ensures teamwork that promotes results and that are consistent with the organization and department's goals. <br>* Duty 7: Has a strong desire to gain the experience necessary for development into a leadership or supervisory position. Practices informal leadership on a daily basis. Provides upwards support for departmental leadership on a routine basis. <br>* Duty 8: Is flexible in scheduling and willingly works in any position on any given day when in the best interest of the department and our patients. <br>* Duty 9: Relays pertinent information in a timely manner to the Corporate Director of Supply Chain to ensure excellent inner-department communication. <br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* High school graduate or equivalent <br>* Strong attention to detail and the ability to work in a fast paced, ever changing environment that includes several different roles <br>* Documented leadership skills and mentoring ability <br>* Positive, service-oriented, interpersonal and communication skills <br>* The individual must be able to physically handle the movement of supplies and equipment as detailed in 'Physical Demands', shown below. <br>PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Degree in Business Administration or related field, or significant work related supply chain experience <br>* CMRP certification or actively working towards certification <br>* Lean/Six sigma yellow belt (or higher) or actively working towards certification <br>* Documented data analysis and performance improvement skills including Microsoft Excel <br>* Accounts payable knowledge <br>* Additional continuing education and/or experience with inventory control practices, supplier contact, expediting and purchasing <br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS<br><br>This position requires a full range of body motion with intermittent walking, lifting, bending, climbing, squatting, kneeling, twisting, sitting and standing. The individual must be able to lift 50 or more pounds occasionally and 35 pounds frequently. The individual must be able to push and/or pull with the aid of a pallet jack (and in some instances the added assistance of another associate) up to 1200 poApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjIwODczLjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Access Control Security Officer (Cincinnati)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237277883]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237277883]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Cincinnati]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45203]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheSecurity Officerposition helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjgyMDU2LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Plastic Assembler Basic (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237183017]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-10]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237183017]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Advanced Drainage Systems Inc]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<STRONG>Advanced Drainage Systems</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>EEO Statement:</STRONG><br><br>Advanced Drainage Systems is proud to be an equal opportunity employer, and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.<br><br><STRONG>Plastic Assembler Basic</STRONG><br><br>US-OH-Findlay<br><br><STRONG>Job ID:</STRONG> 2022-10244<br><STRONG>Type:</STRONG> Regular Full-Time<br><STRONG># of Openings:</STRONG> 1<br><STRONG>Category:</STRONG> Manufacturing<br>Advanced Drainage Systems<br><br><STRONG>Overview</STRONG><br><br>Headquartered in Hilliard Ohio, Advanced Drainage Systems, Inc (ADS) is the leading manufacturer of high performance thermoplastic corrugated pipe, providing a comprehensive suite of water management products and drainage solutions. Our innovative products and superior drainage solutions are used across a broad range of end markets and applications, including residential, non-residential, agriculture and infrastructure applications. We have established a leading position in many of these end markets by leveraging our national sales and distribution platform, overall product breadth and scale, and our manufacturing excellence. Founded in 1966, we operate a global network of 3,700 employees, 63 manufacturing plants and 31 distribution centers. In July, 2014 we became a public company traded on the NYSE&reg;. To enable our continued growth, we are looking to add top talent to our dynamic organization. <br><br><STRONG>Responsibilities</STRONG><br><br>The Plastic Assembler - Basic position is the entry-level title for an associate working in the Fabrication Department. In this position the team member is learning the basics of plastic assembly while actively pursuing next level qualification and certification.<br><br>The responsibilities of this position include, but are not limited to: <br><br><UL><LI>Abide by all safe practices and procedures.</LI><LI>Hot plate welding - Pre-Stub</LI><LI>Continuous involvement in Fabrication/Plant programs and Lean initiatives</LI><LI>Extrusion welding - linear</LI><LI>Actively pursuing qualification for Advanced level</LI><LI>Measuring tools - Basic Level</LI><LI>Engage in cross-functional training.</LI><LI>Material preparation and product finishing</LI><LI>Product knowledge-Plastic Assembler Basic Level</LI><LI>Equipment Operation - Basic Level</LI><LI>Adherence to all quality standards</LI><LI>Specifications - Basic Level</LI><LI>Material handling and scrap management</LI><LI>Understand and practice ADS Core Values.</LI></UL><br><br><STRONG> Job Skills: </STRONG><br><br>This position should possess the following skills/knowledge: <br><br><UL><LI>Strong housekeeping and organizational skills.</LI><LI>Strong interpersonal skills</LI><LI>Mathematics - Geometry</LI><LI>Drawing Interpretation - Basic Level</LI><LI>Hand and Power Tools - Basic Level</LI><LI>Decision making and problem solving abilities</LI></UL><br><br><STRONG> Educational Requirements: </STRONG><br><UL><LI>High School Diploma or equivalent</LI></UL><br><br><STRONG> Preferred Experience: </STRONG><br><br><UL><LI>Carpentry or trade apprenticeship or experience</LI><LI>Metal fabrication or welding.</LI></UL><br><br><STRONG> Physical Requirements: </STRONG><br><UL><LI>The Position requires full range of body motion on a daily basis including twisting, bending, reaching, squatting and ability to mount/dismount industrial equipment and vehicles</LI><LI>The employee will be working specified shifts and moving around at all times, which will require the ability to stand and be mobile for a minimum of 8 continuous hours</LI><LI>Facilities can be extremely hot or cold at times, so the employee must have the ability to perform physical labor for extended periods of time in temperature extremes</LI><LI>The employee will be handling materials daily, which requires the ability to use hands, arms and legs to physically handle and transport finished goods</LI></UL><br><br>Apply Here <br><br>PI164630392]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Other]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Luisa Hernandez</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[jt.sjb@jobtarget.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[RN - Behavioral Health (Orchard Hall) (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237277952]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237277952]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION<br><br>Coordinates total nursing care for patients. Participates inpatient and family teaching and provides leadership by working cooperatively in maintaining standards for professional nursing practice in the clinical setting.<br><br>JOB DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES<br><br>Duty 1: Uses the nursing process to assess, plan, implement, and evaluate patient care to provide for the unique physical and emotional needs of each patient. <br><br>Duty 2: Establishes and maintains communication, and utilizes teaching opportunities to provide for the specific learning needs of each patient and their significant other(s).<br><br>Duty 3: Demonstrates knowledge and skills necessary to provide age appropriate care to the patients served on their unit.<br><br>Duty 4: Collaborates with Physician regarding patient condition, orders, treatment plan, and anticipated needs to ensure exceptional patient care.<br><br>Duty 5: Demonstrates accountability and leadership in the performance of LPN's, Nurse Aides, Orderlies, and Secretaries to ensure quality of patient care and promotion of team collaboration.<br><br>Duty 6: Complies with organizational policies, procedures, and practices to ensure quality job performance and hospital compliance.<br><br>Duty 7: Maintains all department and unit specific competencies for provision of patient care.<br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Licensed by the Ohio Board of Nursing as a Registered Nurse <br>* BLS (within 5 weeks of hire) <br>* Maximum exposure in regard to universal precautions. <br>* Positive service-oriented interpersonal and communication skills <br>* Individual must be able to demonstrate the knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patient served on his/her assigned unit/department. The individual must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to their age-specific needs and to provide the care needed as described in the area's policies and procedures under the direction of the Medical Director. <br>PREFFERED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* 2 year of general nursing experience <br>* Previous psychiatric experience <br>* Certification in psychiatric, mental health nursing <br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS<br><br>This position requires a full range of body motion with intermittent activities in walking, sitting, lifting, bending, squatting, climbing, kneeling, twisting and standing. The associate will be required to lift 50 pounds or more. This position requires individuals to lift work above the Shoulder. The associate must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. Individual must have excellent verbal communication skills to perform daily tasks.<br><br>This position is classified at risk for possible occupational exposure to bloodborne pathogens (HBV, HIV, etc.)Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjg4NzEwLjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Security Officer - Customer Service - $15/hour (Fairborn)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237278074]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237278074]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Fairborn]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45324]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheSecurity Officerposition helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjY3NjExLjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Part Time Consumer Banker I (Wilmington) (Wilmington)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236188113]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-17]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236188113]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[First Financial Bank]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Wilmington]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45177]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[We do the right things, right now. We do them in a way that is relevant to our clients. Become a part of our history as it continues to be written! <br><br>If you are interested and qualified for this role, we invite you to apply.<br><br>The Consumer Banker will work with existing FFB clients and prospect for new FFB clients to deepen client relationships by both booking business directly and by referring, as appropriate, to internal business partners such as Mortgage, Wealth, Small Business Banker Commercial, and Treasury Management.<br><br>Job Description<br><br>Essential Functions/Responsibilities<br><br>* Perform necessary functions necessary to open accounts, perform maintenance.<br>* Run a Teller drawer as deemed necessary by management<br>* Support client engagement through active calling, client conversations, and follow up.<br>* Daily activities that align with The First Financial Bank Experience (FFB Experience), including but not limited to:<br>* Partner with appropriate internal constituencies to bring appropriate level of expertise to the client whether it is service or solution related<br>* Ensure client follow up calls are conducted in the proper time frame.<br>* Maintain all operational and risk management standards<br>* Other duties as assigned to assist clients transact business within the branch, drive-thru, by phone and email.<br>* Model the way for peers and coworkers aligned with First Financials Mission and Values.<br>* The CB is responsible for adherence to all compliance and regulatory procedures.<br>* Client Experience.<br>* Function as client's personal trusted advisor by adding value and building deep client relationships by utilizing the First Client Conversation Model.<br>* Participate and lead in the First Financial Bank Experience by being active in site center huddles and meetings to support sales and service activities.<br>* Consistently meet or exceed sales, service and referral goals as set by management, by effectively collaborating as a team, the District and with lines of business in an effort to assist clients meet their dedicated financial needs.<br>* Provide digital assistance and service for clients establishing or in need of support in utilizing the bank's online offering.<br>* Stay informed and up to date on all bank products, processes and procedures and procedures; especially those that are most complex.<br><br>Minimum Knowledge, Skills, and Abilities Needed to Perform Essential Functions of the Job<br><br>* 2-3 years client service experience in a retail environment.<br>* 2-3 years sales and service experience with previous success in achieving sales and service goals in retail environment.<br>* High school diploma or general education degree (GED) is required.<br>* Associate's degree and/or equivalent work experience in sales is preferred.<br>* Possesses strong sales skills.<br><br>Preferred Knowledge and Skills<br><br>* Associate's degree and/or equivalent work experience in sales is preferred.<br><br>Level of Complexity and Scope<br><br>* Ability to serve a wide variety of client needs according to bank policy and procedures.<br><br>Degree of Independence and Decision-Making<br><br>Required Supervisory Responsibilities<br><br>* None<br><br>Physical Requirements<br><br>* Occasionally lifts and carries up to 20 lbs.<br>* Frequently lifts and carries up to 10 lbs.<br>* Frequently sits, stands, walks and drives<br><br>Compliance Statement<br><br>* The associate is responsible for meeting all compliance requirements imposed on First Financial Bank by State and Federal law and regulation, as well as all related First Financial Bank policies and procedures. This includes all Bank Secrecy Act, Anti-Money Laundering, OFAC and Suspicious Activity rApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjMwOTM4LjEwNTA4QGJhbmthdGZpcnN0Y29tcC5hcGxpdHJhay5jb20]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Customer Support/Client Care]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Sanserrae Frazier</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[hr@bankatfirst.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Multi-Site Security Officer (West Jefferson)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236461408]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-22]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236461408]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[West Jefferson]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[43162]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Reserve Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheReserve Security Officerposition you will be monitoring and patrolling different client sites on a variety of schedules. Helps maintain a safe and secure environment by actively monitoring and patrolling the premise at a variety of client sites. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for client sites pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If your schedule and availability are flexible, and you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjM1NjExLjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Plastic Manufacturing Technician (London)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237278736]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237278736]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Advanced Drainage Systems Inc]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[London]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[43140]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<STRONG>Advanced Drainage Systems</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>EEO Statement:</STRONG><br><br>Advanced Drainage Systems is proud to be an equal opportunity employer, and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.<br><br><STRONG>Plastic Manufacturing Technician</STRONG><br><br>US-OH-London<br><br><STRONG>Job ID:</STRONG> 2022-10252<br><STRONG>Type:</STRONG> Regular Full-Time<br><STRONG># of Openings:</STRONG> 1<br><STRONG>Category:</STRONG> Manufacturing<br>Advanced Drainage Systems<br><br><STRONG>Overview</STRONG><br><br>We seek out the best talent and offer tremendous opportunity for growth, competitive compensation and benefits for individuals who want a career with a great company that maintains a family feel. <br><br><STRONG> Why ADS? </STRONG><br><br> Although our products are typically underground and go unnoticed by most people, we come to work every day to provide cleaner, more sustainable and longer lasting water management products that allow people to live their lives more comfortably and healthily. ADS products prevent fields from eroding and homes from flooding. They keep crops growing, roads and airports in use and prevent contamination of local waterways. <br><br>With a history of breaking new ground and advancing our industry, we are seeking talented people to join our dynamic company. Thanks to our people ADS has become an industry leader and our people recognize the vital role they play in sustaining our environment and water management. <br><br><STRONG>Responsibilities</STRONG><br><br>A Plastic Manufacturing Technician is responsible for the packaging, labeling and visual quality inspection of all products produced on their respective production line. A Plastic Manufacturing Technician is also required to assist Line Operators with line start-ups, shutdowns and tooling changeovers. Partners closely with the Line Operator to meet established production goals. <br><br>This position requires the flexibility to work 40+ hours per week and weekends as required. At ADS we offer both 8 & 12-hour shifts. <br><br>Joining our team has great benefits, here&rsquo;s just a few for our 12-hour shift opportunities: <br><br><STRONG> Work-life balance </STRONG> , with more days off per month you&rsquo;ll enjoy time away from work. You can plan your life around predictable schedules and extra days off for personal interests, hobbies, and wellness activities. <br><br><STRONG> Increased pay </STRONG> as our 12-hour shift will increase take-home pay because you&rsquo;ll earn at least 8 hours of OT each pay period.<br><br><STRONG> Personal Savings </STRONG> as our 12-hour shift employees will have fewer workdays per week which mean fewer hours commuting and lower expenses related to getting to and from work. At ADS this equals six less trips to work per month. <br><br>Whether you want an 8 or 12-hour shift, we have it all available! <br><br><STRONG> Responsibilities: </STRONG><br><br> The responsibilities of this position include, but are not limited to: <br><UL><LI> Embrace a culture of safety </LI><LI> Ensure quality by conducting final visual inspections and labeling all finished goods </LI><LI> Track quantity of units produced from the production line to ensure efficiency </LI><LI> Utilize standard operating procedures to package pipe to be delivered to customers </LI><LI> Maintain a safe working environment that includes the consistent use of Personal Protection Equipment to ensure your safety </LI><LI> Assist with line tooling changes, start-ups, shutdowns and down-stream equipment set-up </LI><LI> Ability to learn and stay current on pipe specifications and packaging requirements </LI><LI> Practice continuous improvement which not only includes the line but also facility housekeeping </LI><LI> Invest in your career with ADS. Build and maintain job skills and additional earning potential through company training programs </LI></UL><br><br><STRONG> Job Skills: </STRONG><br><br> This position should possess the following skills/knowledge: <br><UL><LI> Self-motivated and the ability to work independently </LI><LI> Energetic and thrive in a fast-paced environment </LI><LI> Dependability </LI><LI> Ability to learn new skills </LI><LI> Team oriented </LI><LI> Basic Mathematical skills </LI></UL><br><STRONG> Preferred Experience: </STRONG><br><UL><LI> Previous industrial or manufacturing experience </LI></UL><br><STRONG> Physical Requirements: </STRONG><br><UL><LI> Ability to perform physical labor for extended periods of time in fluctuating temperatures. </LI><LI> Position requires full range of body motion including twisting, bending, reaching, squatting and ability to mount/dismount industrial equipment and vehicles. </LI><LI> Ability to stand and be mobile throughout an 8-12-hour shift. </LI><LI> Ability to use hands, arms and legs to physically handle and transport finished goods. </LI></UL><br><STRONG> Benefits: </STRONG><br><br> We offer a competitive salary and an excellent benefits program including: <br><UL><LI> Medical </LI><LI> Dental </LI><LI> Vision </LI><LI> Retirement Plan </LI><LI> Paid Holidays/ Vacation Days </LI><LI> And much more </LI></UL> <br><br> Apply Here <br><br>PI164761860]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Other]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Luisa Hernandez</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[jt.sjb@jobtarget.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Vehicle Systems Intern - Plant (Parma)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236378673]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-20]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236378673]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[GENERAL MOTORS LLC]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Parma]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44134]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br><br>Responsibilities:<br><br>As a Manufacturing Engineering Intern, you will rotate through a series of positions and assignments in plant and corporate staff locations throughout the United States sought to cultivate development and to educate. These positions are hands-on and engaging. You will learn problem solving on the fly, to work collaboratively with many members of the team, and be able to flex your creative muscles. Most assignments will be located in Warren, MI or Vehicle Assembly Plants in MI. Examples of Manufacturing Engineering assignments available include:<br><br>* Programming of manufacturing technology<br><br>* Analyze product, process and technology to craft best methods to paint & assemble vehicles, and protect the manufacturing process<br><br>* Recommend and validate improvement for existing processes<br><br>* Develop tools to improve program/project management<br><br>* Support development of cybersecurity tools for manufacturing<br><br>* Assists in the design and building of tools and equipment<br><br>* Assists maintenance personnel in operation and maintenance of specialized equipment<br><br>* Troubleshoots special maintenance and equipment problems<br><br>* Coordinates machinery upgrade projects<br><br>About Global Manufacturing Engineering Vehicle Systems Roles & Responsibilities:<br><br>* Responsible for all value-added systems from exit of Body Shop through shipping of finished vehicle<br><br>* Develop & Validate new Manufacturing Technologies and BOE for Automation, Paint, and General Assembly Shops<br><br>* Develop Processes, Machine & Equipment and Tools for 50+ Assembly Plants, 40+ Stamping Plants, and approximately 30 launches each year globally<br><br>* Develop, Validate, and Maintain Common Conveyance Systems and Controls<br><br>* Develop, Validate, and Maintain Cybersecurity Technology to create a secure factory<br><br>* Teams work collaboratively with other centers to reduce energy and waste globally.<br><br>Job locations can be at Manufacturing Engineering headquarters in Warren, Michigan or in various plant locations throughout the U.S. Plant locations may include:<br><br>* Warren, MI<br><br>* Flint, MI<br><br>* Lansing, MI<br><br>* Orion, MI<br><br>* Milford, MI<br><br>* Fort Wayne, IN<br><br>* Arlington, TX<br><br>* Bowling Green, KY<br><br>* Spring Hill, TN<br><br>* Wentzville, MO<br><br>* Fairfax, KS<br><br>* Parma, OH<br><br>* Detroit, MI<br><br>Some travel may be required.<br><br>Additional Job Description<br><br>Qualifications:<br><br>* Currently pursuing a bachelor's degree in Electrical Engineering, Industrial Engineering, Mechanical Engineering, Manufacturing Engineering, Industrial Engineering Technology, Mechanical Engineering Technology, Computer Engineering or Computer Science<br><br>* Able to work fulltime, 40 hours per week<br><br>* Graduating in Spring 2024 or later<br><br>Desired Skills:<br><br>* Knowledge of statistical methods as applied to experimental design and process development<br><br>* Outstanding interpersonal and relationship management skills with the ability to effectively collaborate with varying levels of the organization as needed<br><br>* Excellent written and verbal communication skills with the ability to distill complex subjects to a wider audience<br><br>* Emerging partnership and collaboration skills and ability to learn from and share knowledge with co-workers in a fast-paced environment<br><br>* High level of integrity, ability to deal with ambiguity, take initiative/self-directed<br><br>* Evidence of strong character with integrity, honesty, accountability and trust<br><br>* Consistently demonstrates innovative thinking that is customer-centric<br><br>This role offers the following Work Appropriately strategies:<br><br>* Onsite: This position requires an employee to be on-site on a full-time basis.Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjgyMzkxLjEwNTA4QGdtY29tcGFueWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Logistics/Transportation]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Patricia Smith</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[ofccpcompliance@gm.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Driver - Mileage (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236722258]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-30]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236722258]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Advanced Drainage Systems Inc]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<STRONG>Advanced Drainage Systems</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>EEO Statement:</STRONG><br><br>Advanced Drainage Systems is proud to be an equal opportunity employer, and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability status, protected veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.<br><br><STRONG>Driver - Mileage</STRONG><br><br>US-OH-Findlay<br><br><STRONG>Job ID:</STRONG> 2022-9882<br><STRONG>Type:</STRONG> Regular Full-Time<br><STRONG># of Openings:</STRONG> 4<br><STRONG>Category:</STRONG> Logistics<br>Advanced Drainage Systems<br><br><STRONG>Overview</STRONG><br><br><STRONG> GREAT PAY, GREAT PEOPLE, GREAT PRODUCTS! </STRONG><br><br>We seek out the best talent and offer tremendous opportunity for growth, competitive compensation and benefits for individuals who want a career with a great company that maintains a family feel. <br><br>An <STRONG> ADS Professional Fleet Driver </STRONG> is the link between our company and our customers. We are looking for professional drivers who can deliver the highest level of customer service while maintaining an obsessive focus on safety and personal success. <br><br><STRONG> Why ADS? </STRONG><br><br> Although our products are typically underground and go unnoticed by most people, we come to work every day to provide society cleaner, more sustainable, longer lasting water management products that allow people to continue to live their lives comfortably and healthy. <br><br>ADS products prevent fields from eroding and homes from flooding. They keep crops growing, roads and airports in use and prevent contamination of local waterways. The work we do is highly valuable to society and vitally important to our environment, our planet, our health and our quality of life. Learn more here . <br><br>With a history of breaking new ground and advancing our industry, Advanced Drainage Systems seeks talented people looking to make an impact on a growing, dynamic company. Since our founding, we've built ADS into an industry leader thanks to the work of associates who recognize the vital importance of water management. <br><br>Living a healthy, well-balanced life with the ability to achieve success -- professionally, financially and emotionally -- is what ADS team members want for themselves, and what ADS wants for its team members. <br><br><STRONG>Responsibilities</STRONG><br><br><STRONG> This role offers competitive base pay, quarterly safety incentives, as well as a potential sign on bonus. </STRONG><br><br><STRONG> Our family of Drivers receive: </STRONG><br><UL><LI>Competitive Pay</LI><LI>Sign-on Bonus</LI><LI>Work-life balance - Home most evenings and weekends</LI><LI>Newer, well-maintained equipment</LI><LI>Company-paid uniforms</LI><LI>Local dedicated dispatcher for every driver</LI><li>Paid on hub miles<br></LI><li>Drop pay, paid for all deliveries<br></LI></UL><br> <STRONG>ADS employees receive extremely affordable benefits including:</STRONG> <br><UL><LI> Medical </LI><LI> Telemedicine/Teledoc </LI><LI> Dental </LI><LI> Vision </LI><LI> Paid STD </LI><LI> Voluntary LTD </LI><LI> Employee Stock Ownership Plans </LI><LI> Life Insurance </LI><LI> Flexible Spending Accounts </LI></UL><br> ADS is a dedicated carrier that pays empty and loaded miles, and no slip seating. <br><br><STRONG> Responsibilities include but are not limited to: </STRONG><br><UL><LI> Safe operation of all company equipment </LI><LI> Report BOL discrepancies </LI><LI> Manage safe unloading at delivery destination and place product in customer&rsquo;s desired location </LI><LI> Maintain accurate and up-to-date daily paperwork (trip envelope, RMA&rsquo;s) </LI><LI> Maintain vehicle cleanliness and operational capacity </LI><LI> Adhere to company and departmental policies </LI><LI> Ensure loads are properly secured </LI><LI> Perform pre/post trip inspections of all equipment </LI><LI> Report equipment and payload problems/hazards </LI><LI> Perform in-route inspection of all equipment </LI><LI> Understand and practice ADS CORE VALUES </LI></UL><br><STRONG> Experience: </STRONG><br><UL><LI> One year verifiable OTR experience with reliable carrier. </LI></UL><br><STRONG> Requirements: </STRONG><br><UL><LI> Must possess a valid Commercial Driver&rsquo;s License (CDL) that is applicable for the type of commercial equipment being operated </LI><LI> Must meet/or exceed physical standards of the Federal Motor Carriers Safety Administrations (FMCSA) and ADS </LI><LI> Must have an acceptable Motor Vehicle Record from all states where prior licenses where held </LI><LI> Must be at least 21 years of age (DOT requirement for interstate operation) </LI><LI> Must satisfactory pass all required drug tests </LI><LI> Must pass ADS road test </LI></UL> <br><br> Apply Here <br><br>PI162965785]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Other]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Luisa Hernandez</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[jt.sjb@jobtarget.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Sr. Azure Software Engineer (Cincinnati)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237143604]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-09]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237143604]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Standard Insurance Company]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Cincinnati]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45202]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>Posted Date:</strong> 2022-02-08<br><br><strong>Req ID:</strong> REQ002233<br><br><strong>About Us:</strong> The Standard is a family of companies dedicated to helping its customers achieve financial well-being and peace of mind. In business since 1906, we're a leading provider of group and individual disability insurance, group life, dental and vision insurance, voluntary (employee-paid) benefits, absence management services, and retirement plans and annuities for employers and individuals. For more information about The Standard, visit www.standard.com or follow us on Facebook , Twitter or LinkedIn .<br><br><strong>Description:</strong>At The Standard, you'll join a team focused on putting our customers first.<br><br>Our continued success is driven by a high-performance culture. We're looking for people who are collaborative, accountable, creative, agile and are driven by a passion for doing what's right - across the company and in our local communities.<br><br>We offer a caring culture where you can make a real difference, every day.<br><br>Ready to reach your highest potential? Let's work together.<br><br><strong>- Must be willing to work Pacific time zone -</strong><br><br>Are you passionate about buildingangular applicationsthatdelight customers?JoinTheStandardsoftware engineering team-help us buildnew and modern solutions for our business services!Bring your skills and passionfor front end development, Azure Cloud Services,pipelines,and APIintegrationswith ourapplications andbackend systemstobring peace of mind for our customers. If you enjoycreating new design patterns andare passionateabout thebenefits that thelatest technologies can bring to ouruser experiences,thenthis is the right opportunity for you!<br><br>On our team you will specialize in buildingdigitalapplications that will have abusiness impact. You will be a keyengineer helping tocontinuously enhance ournext generation microservice platform.This will require continuous learning, exploration, tinkering, and creativity. As a member of our team, you will be highly sought after for your knowledge andbe a key influencerincross functionalgroups onhow to solve business problemsthroughdigital applications.You will beexpected to mentor other engineers andhelp them with the adoption of new platforms&technologies.<br><br>As aSoftware Engineer,it'snot just thetechnicalskills you bring to solve technicalproblems,it is the mindset you bring to be part of a great team. We are looking for engineers thatare:<br><ul><li>Driven to Win as a Team:Constantly pursing exceptional results that help us win in the market</li><li>Respect for Teammates:Value diverse identities, backgrounds, talent and perspectives</li><li>Collaboration:Works collaboratively with all team members,integrateperspectives;andencourageothers'contributions</li><li>Adaptable:Quickly adapts tocustomer feedbackby adjusting team priorities to fit new circumstances</li></ul><br><br>Skills <br><ul><li>Ability to work as a collaborative member of agile team, playing varying roles</li><li>Design thinking, creativity, holistic customer centered problem solving, and the ability to bring other team members along</li><li>Ability to perform unstructured work</li><li>Ability tolead and influence others to solve business problems</li><li>Ability to effectively communicateto target audiences</li><li>An inclusive mindsetthat values diversity</li><li>Agile andTestDrivenDevelopment</li><li>Ability to play varying roles</li></ul><br><br>RequiredQualifications <br><ul><li>Bachelor's degree in Computer Science,Information Systems,related technical field, orequivalent experience in an enterprise organization.</li><li>5+ years of software development experience, or ability to demonstrate it didn't take you that long to be at the top of your game</li><li>Demonstrated experience with AzureCloud Services</li><li>Demonstratedexperience withAngularfront endand/orJavaSpringbackendapplicationdevelopment</li><li>Demonstrated experiencebuilding and working with Azure ADO Pipelines</li><li>Experience withcontainerization,Azure Web Apps, and Azure Functions<br>Cosmos/SQL Serverdatabases</li><li>Experience withAzure API Management (APIM)</li><li>Experience with non-structured and structured database systems</li></ul><br><br>Preferred Qualifications <br><ul><li>Experience with Azure Application Configuration Services</li><li>Experiencewithtools like Maven, Git, Jenkins, Azure DevOps, Kubernetes, Docker</li><li>Experience with databases like Cosmos DB,Mongo DB,MS-SQL Server, Oracle</li><li>Experience with frameworks likeAngular Material, Bootstrap</li><li>Experience with REST APIs, Microservices, and Integrations</li></ul><br><br>#LI-SU1<br><br>#LI-Remote<br><br><strong> Note: </strong> The Standard is required to provide a reasonable estimate of the salary for this role when hiring a Colorado resident. The salary for employees working in Colorado in this role is listed below. The Standard's package also includes incentive plan participation and comprehensive benefits including medical, dental, vision, retirement, and paid time off. <br><ul><li>Please note, eligibility to participate in an incentive program is subject to the rules governing the program and plan. Any award depends on various factors, including individual and organizational performance. </li></ul><br><br>Salary Range:<br>$106,500.00 - $186,900.00<br><br>Standard Insurance Company, The Standard Life Insurance Company of New York, Standard Retirement Services, Inc., StanCorp Equities, Inc. and StanCorp Investment Advisers, Inc., marketed as The Standard, are Affirmative Action/Equal Opportunity employers. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, religion, color, sex, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, disability, or veteran status or any other condition protected by federal, state or local law. The Standard offers a drug and alcohol free work environment where possession, manufacture, transfer, offer, use of or being impaired by an illegal substance while on Standard property, or in other cases which the company believes might affect operations, safety or reputation of the company is prohibited. The Standard requires a criminal background investigation, drug test, employment, education and licensing verification as a condition of employment. All employees of The Standard must be bondable.<br><br>Apply Here <br><br>PI164527043]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Other]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Luisa Hernandez</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[jt.sjb@jobtarget.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Multi-Site Security Officer (Grove City)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237281049]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237281049]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Grove City]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[43123]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Reserve Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheReserve Security Officerposition you will be monitoring and patrolling different client sites on a variety of schedules. Helps maintain a safe and secure environment by actively monitoring and patrolling the premise at a variety of client sites. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for client sites pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If your schedule and availability are flexible, and you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjkyMDI5LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Culinary Lead Associate (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237281501]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237281501]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION <br><br>This position is the designed to be a team leader position in the Dietary Department. Duties will be performed in accordance with current applicable federal, state and local standards, guidelines and regulations, Birchaven Village policy and procedure, Birchaven Village ethical statement and resident rights, subject to the Associate Handbook.<br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Minimum 16 years old <br>* Ability to read and comprehend simple instructions, short correspondence and memos. Ability to write simple correspondence. Ability to speak in sentences. <br>* Ability to apply commonsense understanding to carry out instructions furnished in written, oral or diagram form. Ability to deal with standardized situations with only occasional or no variables. <br>* Ability to add and subtract two digit numbers. Ability to count. <br>PREFERED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Experience in customer service preferred. <br>JOB DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES<br><br>Duty 1: Demonstrates the knowledge and skill necessary to provide dietary services to the needs of both internal and external customers.<br><br>Duty 2: Demonstrates leadership and personal accountability for performance to ensure quality food service is given to each and every customer<br><br>Duty 3: Maintains the dietary department in a safe and sanitary manner. Assists in and directs daily cleaning duties <br><br>Duty 4: Prepares meal as needed to comply with therapeutic diets ensuring they are presentable in appearance and palatable<br><br>Duty 5: Prepares food according to specialized recipes and special ordered diets as needed as well as given to the correct customer.<br><br>Duty 6: Ensure that supplies and food are available for the next meal; establish a food production line etc to ensure that all meals are prepared on time.<br><br>Duty 7: Adheres to the unit standards of dress, and attend all scheduled meetings as well as mandatory competency training.<br><br>Duty 8: Displays service excellence as evidenced by practicing the mission and values of the organization to promote resident satisfaction.<br><br>Duty 9: Complies with organizational policies, procedures and practices to ensure quality job performance and regulatory compliance.<br><br>Duty 10: Maintains communications with management regarding all situations.<br><br>Duty: 11: Complete net learning in the assigned time frame and keeping email active<br><br>Duty 12: Be aware of safety hazards and report them promptly<br><br>Duty 13: Assist management in leading their team members to promote a collaborative environment and redirect negative staff as well as assist in problem solving.<br><br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS<br><br>This position requires a full range of body motions with constant walking, lifting, bending, squatting, kneeling, twisting, and standing. The associate will be required to walk/stand for up to eight hours a day. The individual must be able to lift twenty to fifty pounds and reach work above the shoulders. The individual must have good eye-hand coordination and fine finger dexterity for simple grasping tasks. The individual must have excellent verbal communication skills to perform daily tasks. The associate must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. <br><br>*BVHSApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjI3OTA0LjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Senior Integrated Master Scheduler (Fairborn)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237281640]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237281640]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Sumaria Systems, Inc.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Fairborn]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45324]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>Sumaria Systems</strong><br><br><strong>Job Title: </strong>Senior Integrated Master Scheduler<br><br><strong>Job Description: </strong><br><br>Provide scheduling support services for the sustainment and modernization of the F-16 platform.<br><br>Work closely with IPT members, vendors, and other internal and external stakeholders to develop, integrate and maintain project and program Integrated Master Schedules (IMS) using MS Project (or other government-provided software) for the purposes of creating an overarching F-16 Master Schedule.<br><br>Lead discussions and manage planning sessions for IMS baseline development; incorporate contractual and programmatic changes to maintain realistic and current schedule baselines and ability to assist team in forecasting.<br><br>Support includes identification of WBS elements from contractual and programmatic documentation; conversion of data into formats that may be analyzed by IPT for impacts to cost, schedule and resourcing; and briefing IMS draft and final schedules.<br><br>Must be a team player who is able to successfully work with other IMS personnel and external and internal functional personnel (EN, PM, LG, FM, CM, etc.).<br><br>Develops and/or follows organizational scheduling policies and industry best practice and guidelines.<br><br>Will be required to assist Government in developing and delivering training on basic to advanced scheduling methodologies and tool(s).<br><br>Leads discussions and advises management on cost and schedule and resource impacts.<br><br><strong>Required Skills/Education:</strong><br><br>Position requires a minimum of 10 years of acquisition or sustainment logistics experience; possess a working knowledge and independent proficiency in MS Project; and, excellent written and verbal communications skills.<br><br><strong>Education:</strong> Masters Degree<br><br><strong>Years' Experience:</strong> 10 Years<br><br><strong>Travel:</strong> Yes<br><br><strong>Security Clearance Required: </strong>Must have Active Secret clearance to apply.<br><br><strong>Position Type:</strong> Full Time<br><br><strong>Work Location: </strong>WPAFB, Fairborn, Ohio<br><br>Top salaries paid for qualified candidates.<br><br>For more information on Sumaria Systems, please visit our website at www.sumariasystems.com<br><br>Sumaria is an equal opportunity employer and considers qualified applicants for employment without regard to race, color, creed, religion, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity and expression, age, disability, or Vietnam era, or other eligible veteran status, or any other protected factor.<br><br>Sumaria Systems, LLC (Sumaria) is a market leader in Professional Services, Engineering, and Information Technology has been a trusted partner to U. S. Department of Defense communities for more than 30 years. Sumaria Systems only provides engineering services to the federal government, and does not provide professional engineering or surveying services to the public within the meaning of Ohio Revised Code Section 4733.16. With expertise to lead, insight to deliver and commitment to succeed; we staff each mission with a carefully selected team of seasoned professionals. Headquartered in Danvers, MA, with operating locations in Alabama, Colorado, Georgia, Illinois, Ohio, Oklahoma, Utah, and Virginia.<br><br>Apply Here <br><br>PI164767666]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Other]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Larissa Batista</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[recruiting@sumaria.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Senior Systems Safety Engineer - Permanent (Fairborn)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237184777]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-10]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237184777]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Sumaria Systems, Inc.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Fairborn]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45324]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<STRONG>Sumaria Systems</STRONG><br><br><STRONG>Job Title: </STRONG> F-16 System Safety Engineer/Management Support - Permanent<br><br><STRONG>Job Description: </STRONG>Will support the F-16 Program Office's USAF Development Branch as part of the Engineering Group.<br><br>Primary Responsibilities: Interpret and assist with the application of Military Handbook (HIL-HDBK) 516 and other airworthiness requirements to develop and maintain an effective F16 system safety program, to include building Tailored Airworthiness Certification Criteria (TACC) and Modified Airworthiness Certification Criteria (MACC) for F-16 production and modification programs. Assist with the implementation of OSS&E criteria to F-16 production and modification programs. Analyze F-16 aircraft designs and modifications to identify potential hazards. Support the application of system safety principles to identify controls that will effectively eliminate or mitigate hazards. Support aircraft mishap investigations with data and analysis of failure trends and historical information. Review and provide input/corrections to system safety analyses submitted by prime contractors and GFE vendors. Review and provide system safety input/corrections to temporary aircraft modification proposals written by the prime contractor. Interpret DR information received from F-16 operational and test units. Assist with the F-16 program office response to USAF Safety Investigation Board (SIB) recommendations. Use the Air Force Safety Automated System (AFSAS) to update recommendations or review the current status of mishap recommendations. Support F-16 flight testing by reviewing flight test plans and providing hazard identification and mitigation recommendations for each flight test. Serve as a team member on F-16 production and modification programs. Support and document independent system safety assessments and analyses of F-16 production and modification programs and provide recommendations to leadership on hazards and potential mitigations. Assist in RFP development and in evaluation of weapon system contractor proposals in support of F-16 production and modification programs. Assist with writing and assembling of system safety requirements of RFPs including, but not limited to, SRDs, SOWs, CDRLs, and DD Forms 610. Provide input to Government on weapon system contractor performance with respect to system safety requirements. Support activities associated with proposal evaluations including, but not limited to, source selections, technical evaluations, and fact-finding. Support interface with all levels of engineering, program management, and leadership, including, but not limited to, other engineers, lead and chief engineers, technical experts, PMs, and civilian and military leadership within the F-16 Division/FB Directorate, other AFLCMC directorates, AFLCMC headquarters, AFRL, AFMC, ACC, ANG, HQ USAF, DoD, EPAF, FMS air forces, prime and subcontractors, and other Government and private sector personnel. Support various standing F-16 activities and organizations including, but not limited to, the F-16 Consolidated Board, F-16 JMCCT/B, F-16 AB, F-16 CRTs, and F-16 safety groups including SSG, System Safety Working Group (SSWG), and MSTG. Support formal and informal F-16 program reviews and meetings including, but not limited to, risk assessments, requirements and design reviews (e.g. SRR, PDR, CDR), PMRs including pre-PMRs, Management Assistance Team (MAT) meetings, TIMs, and configuration audits.<br><br><STRONG>Required Skills/Education/Experience: </STRONG>Possesses the advanced knowledge, experience and recognized ability to be considered an expert in their technical/professional field, possess the ability to perform tasks and oversee the efforts of junior and journeyman personnel within the technical/professional discipline. Will demonstrate advanced knowledge of their technical/professional discipline as well as possess a comprehensive understanding and ability to apply associated standards, procedures and practices in their area of expertise. (Program Office, Enterprise and Staff Level Support interface)<br><br>Functionally Aligned Minimum Recommended Education and Experience:<br><UL><LI>Successfully completed an undergraduate degree with a major in engineering from a college or university with an Accreditation Board of Engineering and Technology (ABET) accredited engineering program(s) for the degree requirements of the position (e.g. electrical, mechanical, aerospace). Degrees in engineering technology are not considered to be qualifying for these positions. The degree must have been received in the year of, or any year subsequent to the original date of accreditation. To find out if a school has an ABET accreditation, go to ABET accredited schools (http://www.abet.org.</LI><LI>Education / Experience Requirements:<UL><LI>Advanced Degree (Master of Arts (MA) / Master of Science (MS)) and 12 years of experience in the respective technical / professional discipline being performed, five years of which must be in the DoD</LI><LI>OR, BA/BS degree, and 15 years of experience in the respective technical/professional discipline being performed, five of which must be in the DoD</LI><LI>Recommend Industrial Engineer, Electrical Engineer, Mechanical Engineer or Human Factors Engineer ABET accredited degree</LI></UL></LI></UL><br><STRONG>Travel:</STRONG> Yes, 10%<br><br><STRONG>Security Clearance Required: </STRONG> Top Secret clearance or higher is required<br><br><STRONG>Position Type:</STRONG> Full-time 40 hours per week. Hybrid work environment onsite/offsite<br><br><STRONG>Work Location: </STRONG> Wright Patterson AFB, Fairborn, Ohio<br><br>Top salaries paid for qualified candidates.<br><br>For more information on Sumaria Systems, please visit our website at www.sumariasystems.com<br><br>Sumaria is an equal opportunity employer and considers qualified applicants for employment without regard to race, color, creed, religion, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity and expression, age, disability, or Vietnam era, or other eligible veteran status, or any other protected factor.<br><br> Sumaria Systems, LLC (Sumaria) is a market leader in Professional Services, Engineering, and Information Technology has been a trusted partner to U. S. Department of Defense communities for more than 30 years. Sumaria Systems only provides engineering services to the federal government, and does not provide professional engineering or surveying services to the public within the meaning of Ohio Revised Code Section 4733.16. With expertise to lead, insight to deliver and commitment to succeed; we staff each mission with a carefully selected team of seasoned professionals. Headquartered in Danvers, MA, with operating locations in Alabama, Colorado, Georgia, Illinois, Ohio, Oklahoma, Utah, and Virginia. <br><br>Apply Here <br><br>PI164635119]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Other]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Larissa Batista</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[recruiting@sumaria.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Security Officer (Marietta)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237281796]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237281796]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Marietta]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45750]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheSecurity Officerposition helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjEzNzg3LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Security/Protective Services]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Nurse Aide (PT 2nd shift) (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237281798]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237281798]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>STNA SIGN ON BONUS - $2500<br><br>Nurse Aide SIGN ON BONUS - $500<br><br>Birchaven IJ<br><br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION<br><br>The primary purpose of this position is to support the licensed staff by giving direct resident care and performing Nurse aide functions such as care for the personal needs and comfort of residents under the supervision of a Charge Nurse, and in accordance with current applicable federal, state and local standards, guidelines and regulations, Birchaven Village policy and procedure, Birchaven Village ethical statement and resident rights, subject to the employee handbook.<br><br>REQUIRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* High school diploma or equivalent training. <br>* Current registry with the State of Ohio Nurse Aide Registry or have completed Nurse Aide training with valid certificate within 4 months of hire <br>PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS<br><br>* Positive service-oriented interpersonal and communication skills required. <br>* Individual must be able to demonstrate the knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to needs of the residents served on his/her neighborhood. <br>* The individual must demonstrate basic knowledge of the principles related to the aging adult and problems associated with aging. <br>* Possess the ability to assess data reflective of the resident status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each residents needs. <br>PHYSICAL DEMANDS <br><br>This position requires a full range of body motion with intermittent activities in walking, sitting, lifting, bending, squatting, climbing, kneeling, twisting and standing. The associate will be required to lift 50 pounds or more. This position requires individuals to lift work above the shoulder. The associate must have corrected vision and hearing in the normal range. Individual must have excellent communication skills to perform daily tasks.<br><br>This position is classified at risk for possible occupational exposure to bloodborne pathogens (HBV, HIV etc.)Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjkxMTM0LjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Security Officer (Cleveland)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237281890]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237281890]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Cleveland]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44114]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheSecurity Officerposition helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjU3MDkzLjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Security/Protective Services]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Campus Security Officer (Akron)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237282312]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237282312]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Akron]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44308]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheSecurity Officerposition helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjY5Njg2LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Manufacturing Mechanical Engineer Intern (Toledo)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[236135658]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-01-14]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=236135658]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[GENERAL MOTORS LLC]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Toledo]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[43607]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br><br>At General Motors we strive for a culture of excellence. We act with integrity. We are driven by ingenuity and innovation. We have the courage to do and say what's difficult. Each of us takes accountability for results, drives for continued efficiencies and has the tenacity to win.<br><br>We are seeking Manufacturing Mechanical Engineer Interns to do hands-on work that could add directly to the bottom line of our culture and our company. You will have many responsibilities and accountabilities, like mechanical support for programs. You will learn how to lead mechanical projects for several different areas of the plant including operations improvements and new and replacement programs. This is a hands-on position in which you may work with periodic repairs and to provide technical support and direction to support personnel/skilled trades.<br><br>Responsibilities:<br><br>* Mechanical root cause analysis and problem solving<br><br>* Analyze product, process and technology to figure out the best methods of manufacture<br><br>* Assist in the design and building of tools and equipment or recommends improvements to existing processes<br><br>* Assist maintenance personnel in operation and maintenance of specialized equipment<br><br>* Troubleshoot special maintenance and equipment problem<br><br>* Coordinate machinery upgrade projects<br><br>Additional Job Description<br><br>Qualifications:<br><br>* Currently pursuing a bachelor's degree in Mechanical Engineering/Mechanical Engineering Technology<br><br>* Able to work fulltime, 40 hours per week<br><br>* Willing to work in a plant environment<br><br>Desired Skills:<br><br>* Outstanding interpersonal and relationship management skills to effectively collaborate with varying levels of the organization as needed<br><br>* Demonstrates leadership in field of study, extra-curricular activities or service organizations<br><br>* Strong leadership skills, to guide project teams through planning, execution and insight phases<br><br>* Strong critical thinking and analytical skills, especially the ability to synthesize large amounts of data involving multiple variables into comprehensive, applicable insights<br><br>* Ability to work on multiple projects simultaneously, leading timelines and goals<br><br>* Willingness to ask questions, take initiative and be resourceful and inventive<br><br>* Excellent written and verbal communication skills with the ability to distill sophisticated subjects to a wider audience<br><br>* Emerging partnership and teamwork skills and ability to learn from and share knowledge with co-workers in a rapidly moving environment<br><br>* High level of integrity, ability to deal with ambiguity, takes initiative/self-directed<br><br>* Evidence of strong character with integrity, honesty, accountability and trust<br><br>* Deliver new and creative solutions to sophisticated problems<br><br>This role offers the following Work Appropriately strategies:<br><br>* Onsite: This position requires an employee to be on-site on a full-time basis.<br><br>The start date for these Internship roles are for May & June of 2022 Spring/Summer Internship<br><br>GM will provide a one-time lump sum taxable stipend payment to each student selected for the 2022 Student Program<br><br>PLEASE ONLY APPLY IF YOU DO NOT NEED SPONSORSHIP TO WORK IN THE UNITED STATES NOW OR IN THE FUTURE. WE ARE UNABLE TO CONSIDER CANDIDATES WHO REQUIRE SPONSORSHIP.<br><br>About GM<br><br>Our vision is a world with Zero Crashes, Zero Emissions and Zero Congestion and we embrace the responsibility to lead the change that will make our world better, safer and more equitable for all.<br><br>Why Join Us<br><br>We aspire to be the most inclusive company in the world.Apply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjg0MzA1LjEwNTA4QGdtY29tcGFueWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Logistics/Transportation]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Patricia Smith</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[ofccpcompliance@gm.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Machine Operator (Sidney)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237282565]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237282565]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[AMG Solutions, Inc.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Sidney]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45365]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Purpose: Producing Quality parts per Customer specifications.<br><br>Duties:<br>* Maintaining a clean and safe work space.<br><br>* Prepares machine for production by positioning and securing part on fixture.<br><br>* Regulates machining by setting and adjusting controls.<br><br>* Filing and Deburring after machining is complete.<br><br>* Maintains specifications by observing operations; detecting malfunctions; inspecting parts; adjusting controls; replacing broken tooling.<br><br>* Resolves production problems by notifying supervisor to obtain additional resources.<br><br>* Documents actions by completing production and quality logs.<br><br>* Contributes to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed.<br><br>Skills/Qualifications:<br>Strong math skills, reading of gauges, mics and calipers.]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Manufacturing/Production/Operations]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Amanda Laux</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[amandalaux@aandbmachine.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Access Control Security Officer (Cleveland)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237283113]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237283113]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[SECURITAS SECURITY SERVICES USA, INC.]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Cleveland]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[44114]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Security Officer <br><br>We help make your world a safer place. <br><br>Securitas is a global company that offers the most advanced and sustainable security solutions in the industry. We are located in 47 countries and have 355,000 employees worldwide and over 150,000 clients. <br><br>Securitas plays an essential role for our clients and in society. TheSecurity Officerposition helps maintain a safe and secure environment for our clients by actively monitoring the premises, including patrolling a variety of locations. They preserve order while enforcing regulations and directives for a client site pertaining to personnel, visitors, and the area. Frequently our Security Officers will provide customer service and information to a client's employees and customers. <br><br>We are driven by a clear corporate culture and purpose, which helps us live according to our values ofIntegrity, Vigilance, and Helpfulness.These values are at the heart of our culture, help define who we are and guide our actions. <br><br>No experience necessary! If you have retail, food service or hospitality industry background you are a great fit for this role; if not, we will provide you with the training and everything you need for a great introduction to a career in the security industry. <br><br>Are you interested in being part of our Team? <br><br>* Apply quickly and efficiently online <br><br>* Interview from the convenience of your own home <br><br>* Weekly pay <br><br>* Competitive benefits <br><br>* Flexible schedules <br><br>With over 80 years of protecting the things that matter, we've seen more than most. That's why Securitas is the partner of choice for companies and an employer of choice for candidates worldwide. <br><br>See a different world. <br><br>EOE/M/F/Vet/DisabilitiesApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjQ2MjU1LjEwNTA4QHNlY3VyaXRhc2luY2NvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance/Safety]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Janine Steigerwald</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[sssusa@ajecompliance.com]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title><![CDATA[Director of IT Applications & Innovation (Findlay)]]></title>
      <referencenumber><![CDATA[237283284]]></referencenumber>
      <date><![CDATA[2022-02-11]]></date>
      <url><![CDATA[http://jobseeker.ohiomeansjobs.monster.com/jobview/GetJob.aspx?JobId=237283284]]></url>
      <company><![CDATA[Blanchard Valley Regional Health Center]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Findlay]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[Ohio]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
      <postalcode><![CDATA[45840]]></postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Description<br>PURPOSE OF THIS POSITION<br><br>The Director of IT Applications & Innovation is responsible for the development and implementation of information technology applications (clinical, business, etc...) as well as providing analysis and programming activities to improve business processes. Standard managerial responsibilities include managing staff, budgeting, reporting and providing overall direction and guidance. Establishing benchmarks and assuring these goals are met within the IT department is another aspect of this position.<br><br>A strong knowledge of IT, applications and project management is essential. Since identifying the organization's needs is a major part of this role, a thorough understanding of and over five years prior experience working in a healthcare or hospital environment is required, with at least three years in a leadership position.<br><br>JOB DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES<br><br>Duty 1: Staff Management - Collaborates with CIO to ensure appropriate IT staff via effective recruitment, retention and development<br><br>Duty 2: Strategy & Planning - Collaborates with CIO and IT Leadership on emerging technology opportunities and disruptive expectations. Develops strategy to manage opportunity and minimize risks. Understands current environment and integration opportunities, including assisting in preparing a roadmap for strategic plan, emerging technology and integration opportunities.<br><br>Duty 3: Strategy & Planning - Partners with business or clinical leaders to analyze, develop, and identify IT needs for existing and future planned initiatives; determines scope and priorities for these initiatives and provides guidance to customers on IT governance processes. Participates in the development and implementation of the Strategic IT Plan, projecting resource requirements, costs and project planning. Develops and communicates roadmap and expectations on meeting the strategic initiatives acting as an advocate, mentor and change agent with the team to build consensus.<br><br>Duty 4: Acquisition & Deployment - Stays current on industry trends and regulatory changes. Researches emerging technology and analyzes the organizational opportunity and risk mitigation requirements. Understands and educates BVHS leaders on the impact of Cerner's development cycle on the BVHS strategic plan. Maintains roadmaps of anticipated organizational needs, IT advancements, regulatory requirements and solution/feature availability. Utilizes this information to assist various directors in understanding how technology will impact their areas and needs.<br><br>Duty 5: Acquisition & Deployment - Oversees the development of detailed project schedules and manages the project budget, assessments, and service level agreements. Assists project managers on understanding and managing action items, risks/issues and all project deliverables. Facilitating project meetings and generating agendas/minutes. Driving projects through all deployment phases while reviewing project performance, and effect changes as needed to improve business processes and support critical business strategies. <br><br>Duty 6: Operational Management - Establishes policies, procedures, standards and objectives for applications management with the rest of the IS leadership team. Ensures that the system portfolio list is kept updated and relevant with impact analysis on each change, including version, upgrades, system capacity, hardware requirements, additional features/functionality and required resources. Maintains documentation of all current integration points (hardware/software) that would be impacted by changes to any of the systems<br><br>Duty 7: Operational Management - Collaborates with IS team to develop integration and interoperability opportunities and strategy. Defines strategies and approaches for the effective sharing of information between systemApply here: https://www.aplitrak.com/?adid=YmJnZW5lcmljLjg0MjgzLjEwNTA4QGJsYW5jaGFyZHZhbGxleWNvbXAuYXBsaXRyYWsuY29t]]></description>
      <salary/>
      <jobtype><![CDATA[Employee]]></jobtype>
      <category><![CDATA[Medical/Health]]></category>
      <budget/>
      <recruiternames>
         <recruitername>Tami Risner</recruitername>
      </recruiternames>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail><![CDATA[tjrisner@bvhealthsystem.org]]></recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
      <price/>
   </job>
</source>
