<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<source xmlns="http://brazen.com/jobs/">
   <publisher>Brazen Technologies</publisher>
   <publisherurl>https://brazen.theresumator.com/</publisherurl>
   <lastbuilddate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 20:03:03 GMT</lastbuilddate>
   <job>
      <title>Lead/Senior Quality Assurance Engineer</title>
      <date>2019-01-28T07:53:26</date>
      <referencenumber>987654321</referencenumber>
      <url>https://brazen.theresumator.com/apply/0Q3QZnzzNL/LeadSenior-Quality-Assurance-Engineer</url>
      <company><![CDATA[Brazen Technologies]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Arlington]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[VA]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
      <postalcode>22209</postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[<i>Join a small company who is making great strides in the hiring sector!</i>

<h1>Who We Are</h1>
At Brazen, we believe everyone deserves a job they love - including you. We're a venture-backed SaaS startup focused on changing the way organizations engage their audiences online. Recently voted one of DC's top 50 best places to work by the Washingtonian, we're looking for energetic, self-starting technologists to supplement our team.

Our chat platform offers employers, universities, publishers, and associations an innovative way to connect and chat with their stakeholders. Organizations like Microsoft, Northrop Grumman, and hundreds of colleges and universities leverage our technology every day to change the way they bring people together.



<h1>The Position</h1>
We are looking for a Senior Quality Assurance Engineer/Lead to lead the testing of our core product.

<h2>Responsibilities:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Develop and refine verification criteria for user stories with the product team.</li>
<li>Lead test cases execution based on new functional specifications.</li>
<li>Shape and lead the defect discovery and resolution process.</li>
<li>Create, maintain, and execute regression testing of the core application.</li>
<li>Execute load testing and maintain baseline performance metrics.</li>
<li>Document, troubleshoot, and isolate problems encountered during testing.</li>
<li>Own the quality assurance of each release.</li>
<li>Work with the customer service and account management teams to identify, diagnose, and isolate bugs, issues, and new feature requests.</li>
<li>Establish and maintain an intimate working knowledge of the core product.</li>
</ul>

<h2>Required Qualifications:</h2>
<ul>
<li>5 years experience testing software applications.</li>
<li>Development experience in any programming language.</li>
<li>Experience working as a Scrum or Kanban team member.</li>
<li>Self-motivated team player able to work in a dynamic environment.</li>
<li>Must be able to work both independently and as part of a team and thrive on technical challenges.</li>
</ul>

<h2>Desired Qualifications:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Experience testing Java applications.</li>
<li>Experience testing Web applications</li>
<li>Experience writing automated test suites in Selenium or a similar tool.</li>
<li>Experience leading testing of a mid to large sized application.</li>
</ul>

<h1>Perks</h1>
<ul>
<li>Competitive Salary</li>
<li>401k</li>
<li>Excellent health benefits</li>
<li>Catered Lunches and free snacks/drinks</li>
<li>View of the Washington Monument, National Cathedral and Georgetown University from your desk!</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <category>Engineering</category>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail>sam@brazen.com</recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
   </job>
   <job>
      <title>Business Development Representative</title>
      <date>2019-02-04</date>
      <referencenumber>876543219</referencenumber>
      <url>https://brazen.theresumator.com/apply/01lat8jChI/Business-Development-Representative</url>
      <company><![CDATA[Brazen Technologies]]></company>
      <city><![CDATA[Arlington]]></city>
      <state><![CDATA[VA]]></state>
      <country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
      <postalcode>22209</postalcode>
      <description><![CDATA[Who we are

At Brazen, we believe everyone deserves a job they love. Including you. If you’re in search of a job you love, then you've come to the right place. 

Brazen is a fast growing, venture backed SaaS startup in Arlington, VA (Court House Metro). We are fundamentally changing the way professionals find new opportunities and employers connect with job seekers. If the idea of working for a rapidly growing SaaS start-up in a fast-paced environment sounds like the challenge and opportunity you’re looking for, read on.

What we do

Our conversational recruiting platform (including live chat, AI-powered chatbots, scheduled chat and online events) offers employers, universities, and associations an innovative way to connect and chat with their stakeholders. Organizations like Deloitte, KPMG, Raytheon, American Express and dozens of colleges and universities leverage our technology everyday to change the way they bring people together and communicate.

What we’re looking for

We’re searching for a dynamic, ambitious and talented Business Development Representative (BDR) to join our team. As a BDR, you will be responsible for generating and qualifying new leads and booking qualified meetings for our Business Development Managers (BDM). 

To be successful in this role, you should have experience in developing and nurturing your own sales funnel. Additionally, you'll need strong communication skills, both written and verbal, and the ability to build relationships with prospects. Successful BDRs are also adept at identifying prospect needs and pain points and properly positioning the value of the Brazen platform. 

This is an incredibly exciting opportunity to get on the ground level of a young, fast growing SaaS company where you can develop your career around bright, ambitious professionals.

Here is an overview of the primary responsibilities:

Manage Leads - Help identify and develop lists of new prospects in both existing and emerging markets, as well as pre-qualify all leads by determining organizational fit, budget level, authority, need and timeline. You will also use HubSpot, Salesforce and a sales engagement platform to identify opportunities and manage your day.

Set Meetings - In partnership with marketing, you will follow up with those contacts that have engaged with either outbound sales emails or marketing emails to set qualified meetings for business development managers. You will have a monthly, quarterly and annual goal for meetings as well as contribution to closed sales.

Communicate value - Become a product expert. Learn our product inside and out and be able to articulate the features, benefits and most importantly the value to your prospects.

Refine process - Measure performance, determine what’s working and what isn’t, and help to refine our sales process. You will provide feedback to the sales team and marketing team to help ensure we’re reaching the right people at the right organizations. You’ll also work closely with the business development managers to improve processes and quality of meetings.

Brazen is a group of about 30 people so you will have a unique opportunity to work very closely with our Director of Marketing to target prospects, our VP of Business Development to learn the ins and outs of how to identify and qualify a lead and our Founder and CEO to understand the business from the inside out.   

This role is a critical piece of the Brazen sales process, but it’s also a time for you to learn the business, help us craft a scalable sales process and prepare for an inside sales role at Brazen.  We’re a fast growing company and offer our sales & account management team with opportunities that can re-define your career.  Again, we believe everyone deserves a job they love, and we take that very seriously. The growth opportunities at Brazen are limitless if you are willing to work hard, give it your all and hit your numbers!

Qualifications and Skills

1-2 years experience in sales or appointment setting role
Obsessed with and driven by RESULTS
Superior organizational skills
Ability to put together a plan, follow through on the plan and assess how to improve
Adaptability
Ability to thrive in a fast-paced, dynamic, very high activity sales role
Scrappy work ethic with a “anything it takes” attitude to achieving a goal
Ability to work in a self-starter environment
Top-notch communication and presentation skills with the ability to creatively sell to all decision-making levels
Team-player mentality
Ability to make 75+ outbound calls and send out multiple targeted emails on a daily basis
Extra credit for...

Experience utilizing CRM (ideally Salesforce) or marketing automation systems (e.g. HubSpot, Marketo)
Experience in the talent acquisition space
Interest in developing or growing a career in software/technical sales or account management
The Benefits You’ll Get:

Competitive Base + high commission potential
Fun, fast paced startup environment with enormous opportunity for growth
Medical, Dental, Vision
401K
Great vacation policy
Flexibility in regard to work hours and responsibilities
Free snacks (we’re currently on a Beef Jerky and almonds kick, but we take requests)]]></description>
      <category>Sales</category>
      <recruiteremails>
         <recruiteremail>sam@brazen.com</recruiteremail>
         <recruiteremail>drew@brazen.com</recruiteremail>
      </recruiteremails>
   </job>
</source>